少 数 派 报 告
- 你知道没有了他们我会多么迷茫吗? - 别哭 霍华德
- You know how blind I am without them. - Howard don't cry.
谋杀!
Murder!
[受害者] 撒拉·马克思 唐纳·杜宾
- 祝你好运 约翰 - 身体不舒服吗?
- Good luck, John. - Any contractions?
只有你给我的那一下
Only the ones you give me.
2054年
[凶犯] 霍华德·马克思
- 好的 杰德 什么情况? - 红球...双重杀人事件 被害人一男一女
- Okay, Jad, what's coming? - Red ball...double homicide, one male, one female.
凶手是男性 白人 40岁
Killer's male, white, 40's.
影像时间在早上8:04
Aggregated the time frame at 8:04 a.m.
影像有些模糊 所以地点还没有确定
The twins are a little fuzzy on that, so we need a confirmation.
凶案地点仍未查出 鉴定人已联接入系统...
Location still uncertain. Remote witnesses are plugged in...
这被立为第1108号案件
This will be case #1108.
1108号案件 根据预测师影像 指控未来杀人罪
Case #1108, previsualized by the Precogs and recorded on holosphere by Precrime's q-stacks.
1108案鉴定人 金凯瑟琳博士和波拉德法官
My fellow witnesses for case #1108 are Dr. Katherine James and Chief Justice Frank Pollard.
- 早上好 - 早上好
- Good morning. - Good morning.
鉴定人 审查1108号案的工作 现在可以开始吗?
Will the witnesses preview and validate #1108 at this time?
- 批准 - 开始吧
- Affirmative I will validate. - Go get him.
遵命...
Stand by...
谋杀发生时间为早上8:04 离现在还有44分30秒 这是红球(凶杀案件)
Time of murder: 08:04 a.m. That is 44 minutes 30 seconds from now.
霍华德·马克思 你究竟在哪里?
Alright, Howard Marks, where are you?
霍华德 吃早餐了
Howard! Howard, breakfast!
87年前...
Four score and seven years ago...
他有点脸熟
He looked familiar.
- 谁? - 那个站在街对面公园的男人
- Who? - The man standing in the park across the street.
- 我以前见过他 - 你没戴眼镜怎么认得? 你知道你有多近视
- I have seen him before. - How can you even tell, you know how blind you are without your glasses.
- 你的眼镜放哪了? - 可能放在卧室里了
- Where are your glasses? - I must have left them up in the bedroom.
你快就要迟到了...
You're running out of time...
你知道我有多迷茫...
You know how blind I am...
我在辖区内查到八个"霍华德·马克思" 年龄 人种都符合
I show eight "Howard Marks" in the District. Sorted by race and age.
去找执照登记 看看能有什么线索
Run the licence and registration. See if we can capture him this way.
你能办得到吗?
Can you grab that?
还不知道
It's unclear.
- 我有六张符合要求的执照 你认为是哪个? - 就在这
- I got six licences what do you want? - Over here, please.
他们在金斯保罗区福克斯路4221号
Got him in the Foxhall. 4421 Gainsborough.
派一个行动组过去 在河边设置警戒线
Send a DCPD blue & white. Set up a perimeter of the river.
我在想今天我或许 可以不去上班 在家里呆着
You know I was thinking maybe I'd play hooky. Stay home today.
我们可以去郊游...
We have come to dedicate a portion of that field...
你觉的怎么样?
What do you think?
好好的休息一下... 那你的会议怎么办?
Become a resting place...what about your meeting?
我会改期 最近一直都在忙着工作了
I'll reschedule. I've been working too much anyway.
我们可以共进午餐
We can have lunch together.
我也想...我也很想这样 但是
I would love...I would love to.
我还要打扫房间
I have an opening house like the rest of the place
我想这就是你看起来如此可爱的原因
I guess that's why you look so nice.
长官! 我们对于案发地点的定位有麻烦了
Chief! We got a problem with our location.
- 他们已经不住那了 - 见鬼!
- It's no longer there. - Shit!
- 还有多少时间? - 30分钟
- Time frame? - 30 minutes.
- 约翰 调查局的朋友来了 - 我现在最需要的就是 那些调查局的饭桶离我远点
- Chief, the investigator from the Fed is here. - All I need is some twink from the Fed poking around right now.
约翰 信息传到了你的电脑里 我也给你家留了信息...
John, the word is on your counter, I left your message at your house...
再查一下那片纸上的内容 问问他们的邻居是否知道他们去哪了 还有他们的亲戚...
Check again with the paper, they had it forwarded. See if the neighbors know where they went, check all relations...
查一下他们所有的亲戚邻居
Checking neighbors and their relations...
- 但是约翰... - 给他一杯咖啡
- But John... - Fletch just get him some coffee.
给他讲讲我们每天如何保全人们性命的事 如果没有我你们就不一定活着了
Tell him some stories how I save your ass everyday, and you can't live without me.
我已经有咖啡了 谢谢
I got coffee, thank you.
丹尼·维特沃 "调查局的饭桶" 哦 要口香糖吗?
Danny Witwer. The "Twink from the Fed". Woops. Gum?
对不起 丹尼 但我现在没时间陪你四处去转
Sorry Danny, but I'll have to give you the full tour some other time.
马克斯一家两个星期前搬走 没有人知道他们去了哪 仍然在调查
The Marks have moved two weeks ago. Nobody knows where. Still searching for family and employer.
还剩12分钟
Time horizon: 12 minutes...
我们称他正在做的事叫做重组影像 找寻即将发生的谋杀案地点的线索
What he's doing now, we call "scrubbing the image", looking for clues as to where the murder's going to happen.
砖墙的堆砌有佐治亚风格...
Original running bond brick pattern, streamlined early Georgian Details...
砖墙被重漆过
The brick has been repainted.
- 这个国家 - 这个国家
- And that this nation. - And that this nation.
- 在上帝的保佑下 - 在上帝的保佑下
- Under God. - Under God.
- 决不会从地球上消失 - 决不会从地球上...
- Shall not perish from the earth. - Shall not perish from the...
受害者的名字从这里出来 而凶手的名字在这边
Victims are pronounced here. Killers here.
还有犯罪的时间 其他的线索 我们要靠分析他们生成的那些影像
Beyond that, the date of the crime, all we have to run on are the images, that they produce.
- 一个警察骑在马背上 - 靠近首都?
- I show a cop on horseback. - Near the capital?
- 没有磁悬浮系统 - 林荫道?
- No maglev system. - The mall?
佐治镇
Georgetown.
预言者可以提前四天就知道凶手? 那叫什么来着?
The Precogs can see a murder four days out. What are that liked called?
嗯 我们叫它红球
Well, we call it the Red Ball.
这些犯罪情绪通常都不是预谋的 所以他们会感知的比较晚
The crimes of passion is no premeditation so they show up late.
大多数案件是类似现在这样瞬间发生的
Most of our scrambles are flash events like this one.
现在很少见到预谋杀人了
We rarely see anything with premeditation anymore.
人们已经明白这个意思了
People have gotten the message.
哦 这太好了
Oh this is good.
德文特·金斯利 十八世纪建筑师 他在华盛顿建了至少两打这类的房子
I show a match a for Dwight Kingsley. Eighteen century architect. He did two dozen houses in D.C.
剩余10分钟...
Time horizon, ten minutes...
十分钟!
Ten minutes!
看这个孩子
Look at this kid.
在这个影像里他在穿西服的男人左边
In this one, he's on the left of the man in the suit.
- 是的 那又怎么样? - 在这个影像里他变成在右边了
- Yes, so? - This one he is on the right.
转转椅
Merry-go-round.
那是个公园
It's a park.
本市这样的老式转转椅的公园 只有十六个
There's only sixteen of those old merry-go-rounds left in the city.
佐治镇有两个 一个在巴纳比森林 另一个在维里
Two in Georgetown. One in Barnaby Woods, the others in Woodley.
维里都是维多利亚式建筑 肯定是在巴纳比森林 飞过去要多久?
Woodley's all Victorian. It's gotta be Barnaby Woods. Evanna flight time?
如果我开的话 三分钟就能到
When I drive. Three minutes and the wheel's up.
- 好了吗? - 好了!
- Clear? - Clear!
好了!
Clear!
剩余时间6分钟
Time horizon: 6 minutes...
- 我们去床上好吗? - 就在这吧
- Let's go to bed. - Let's do it in here.
- 床比较软 - 我也很软
- The bed is soft. - I'm soft.
见鬼!
Shit!
到底是哪一个?
Which one is it?
只剩1分钟了 长官 我们必须采取下一步行动了
Time horizon: 1 minute. Chief, we've catching up to the future.
闭嘴 爱万娜 杰德?
Shut up Evanna. Jad?
- 杰德? - 请讲
- Jad? - Go ahead.
- 他关前门了吗? - 什么?
- Did he close the front door? - What?
马克思关前门了吗? !
Did Marks close the front door?!
没有 前门是开着的 前门开着!
Negative. The front door is open! The front door is open!
剩余时间30秒
Time horizon: 30 seconds...
- 我忘了我的眼镜 - 哦 霍华德
- I forgot my glasses. - Oh. Howard.
你知道如果我失去了眼镜 会有多么迷茫吗?
You know how blind I am without them.
霍华德 别哭
Howard don't cry.
马克思!
Marks!
看着我 看着我
Look at me. Look at me.
确认是霍华德·马克思
Positive for Howard Marks.
马克思先生
Mr. Marks.
遵照哥伦比亚特区犯罪预防部门的命令
By mandate of the District of Columbia Precrime division, -
我们以即将谋杀撒拉·马克思 和唐纳德·杜宾的罪名逮捕你...
- I'm placing you under arrest for the future murder of Sarah Marks and Donald Doobin, -
该凶杀案本应在今天 4月22日 8点零4分发生
- that was to take place today, April 22, at zero-eight hundred hours, four minutes.
不 我什么也没有做 撒拉!
No. I didn't do anything. Sarah!
给这位先生戴上帽子
Give the man his hat.
哦 上帝 别把那个环套在我头上
Oh, God. Don't put the halo on me!
- 撒拉! - 手放到头上!
- Sarah! - Put your hand on your head!
救救我! 我没打算干什么的
Help me! I wasn't gonna do anything!
为什么你不稍微安静几分钟听我说
Why don't you just sit here a minut a listen to me.
你的丈夫已被预防罪案部逮捕
Your husband has been arrested by officers from Precrime.
哦 上帝 霍华德! 不!
Oh, God Howard! No!
霍华德 别哭!
Howard, don't cry!
霍华德 别哭了
Howard, please don't cry!
哦 天那 哦 天那
Oh, God! Oh, God!
我想他们阻止了谋杀
I thought they stopped the murder.
那只是重复的回想
That's just an echo.
一种预言师的记忆幻觉
A Precog deja vu, if you will.
糟糕的是他们总是 一次又一次看见犯罪场景
The really bad ones, the Precogs see over and over again.
华利 切断传输
Wally. Erase the incoming.
想像一个没有谋杀的世界
Imagine a world without murder.
我失去了我最好的朋友
I lost my best friend.
- 我失去了我的姨妈 - 我失去了爸爸
- I lost my aunt. - I lost my dad.
- 我失去了我父亲 - 我失去了我妻子
- I lost my father. - I lost my wife.
就在六年前这个国家的谋杀案 达到前所未有的高峰
Just six years ago the homicide rate in this country had reached epidemic proportions.
看来只有奇迹才能阻止这些凶杀
It seemed that only a miracle could stop the bloodshed.
但我们得到了不止一个奇迹 而是三个 我们的犯罪预言师
But instead of one miracle we were given three. The precognitives.
仅仅在预防罪案计划 开始实施的一个月内
Within just one month under the Precrime programme.
哥伦比亚特区的凶杀案 就大幅下降90％
The murder rate in the District of Columbia was reduced 90 percent.
他们可能已经在车里等着我
They were gonna be waiting for me in the car.
他可能会强奸我
He was gonna rape me.
- 我本来应该被刺穿了 - 就在这
- I was gonna be stabbed. - Right here.
一年之内
Within a year.
预防罪案部在我们首都 有效地制止了凶杀案的发生
Precrime has affectively stopped murder in our nation's capital.
这六年来 我们一直在进行我们的试验
In the six years we have been conducting out little experiment.
再没有发生一起谋杀案
There hasn't been a single murder.
现在犯罪预防部在为你们工作
And now Precrime can work for you.
他们要确保每一个美国人 都在这个系统的有效保护之下
We want to make absolutely certain that every American can bank of the utter availability of the system.
不仅保证我们的安全 也保证我们的自由
And to make sure that not only keeps us safe... but also keep us free.
- 预防犯罪部 非常有效! - 非常有效!
- Precrime: It works! - It works!
- 有效! - 有效!
- It works! - It works!
预防犯罪部 非常有效!
Precrime: It works!
请在4月22日 星期二 投票支持预防犯罪部
On Tuesday April 22, vote Yes on the National Precrime Initiative.
怎么回事 睡不着吗?
What's the matter, can't sleep?
我只是需要一些货
I just need a little clarity.
当然 你想要平常的那种还是新改良型的?
True that. You want the customary clarity, or the new and improved kind of clarity?
给我些新货
Just give me the new stuff.
祝你好梦 长官
Sweet dreams, Chief.
不必担心 我会为你保守秘密的 而且从中我也可以捞到好处
Don't worry none, your secret's safe with me. Besides I could use little juice on my side.
你以为你知道什么 洛克?
What do you think you know, Lycon?
正如我爸爸所说:
It's like my Daddy used to say:
"在瞎子的国度..."
"In the land of the blind..." -
"有一只眼睛就能成为国王"
"The one eyed-man is King".
我回来了
I'm home.
顶灯
Overhead.
墙面荧幕
Wallscreen.
- "肖恩" - "嘿 爸爸"
- "Sean!" - "Hi Daddy!"
"你能教我如何跑的更快吗? "
"Can you teach me how to run faster?"
"因为班上所有的小朋友都跑的比我快"
"Because all the kids at my class run faster than me."
"不"
"No."
你看 抬起你的膝盖
Look! Keep your knees up!
就像这样 像这样
Like that. Like that.
高一点 就像那样 你是个天生的跑步好手
High, high. Like that. See you are a natural runner.
"一直跑! "
"Gotta keep running!"
是的 一直跑
Yeah. Gotta keep running!
一直跑
You gotta keep running.
"我将来能和你跑的一样快吗? "
"Will I be as fast as you some day?"
你将来一定能赢过我
I think you will beat me some day.
你会赢过所有人
I think you will be everyone some day.
"我要走了..."
"I gotta go..."
- "再见" - 不 不 等等
- "Bye." - No, no, wait wait.
- 你必须吻我一下 - "不亲嘴唇"
- You gotta give me a kiss. - "Not on the lips!"
"只有妈妈才能亲我嘴唇"
"Only mummy kisses me on the lips."
我爱你
I love you.
- 我爱你 肖恩 - 我爱你 爸爸
- "I love you, Sean." - I love you daddy!"
"你让我想起了那个海滩"
"You reminds me of Roserito Beach."
"记得吗? "
"Remember?"
我们身上只有20美元 我们去度假 坐在车里 阳光明媚
"Yeah...we had 20 dollars, and waited in the van so the sun would shine on our vacation."
"约翰 约翰 把摄像机关掉"
"John. John. John put the camera down."
"看 我...我准备睡觉了 这是什么 不"
"Look, I'm...I'm all ready for bed...what...what is this? No."
"把它拿开 该去睡了"
"Put it away, it's time to put the camera to sleep."
"该去照顾你的妻子了"
"And time to come and take care of your wife."
"甜心 为什么不放下摄像机"
"Sweetie, why don't you put the camera down," -
"和我一起看雨景吧"
"and come and watch the rain with me."
"不? 我保证这会是难忘的记忆"
"No? I promise to make it a memorable moment."
"听着 要么放下摄像机 要么你今晚什么也得不到"
"Look. Put the camera down or you are not getting anything tonight."
一个司法部的家伙 想夺走我们的一切
A gentleman from Justice wants to take all this away from us.
你知道 一星期以后人们就要投票...
You understand a week from now people are going to vote on -
决定我们是否能在这里 继续我们的思路
- whether or not what we've been doing down here has been some noble-minded enterprise -
...或者获得改变 本市治理犯罪的方式的机会
- or a chance to change the way this country fights crime.
我明白 先生
I understand. Sir.
约翰 小心丹尼·维特沃
John. Watch this Danny Witwer.
- 司法部派来的观察员 - 是的 我昨天见过他了
- The observer from Justice. - Yes, I met him yesterday.
- 你可以让他四处转转 回答他的问题 但要盯住他 - 是的 先生
- You can let him look around, answer his questions, but watch him. - Yes, sir.
- 如果有任何问题 第一时间通知我 - 我知道
- And if there is any problem, make sure we know about it first. - I understand.
一旦预言师确定了 一名受害者和凶手...
When the Precogs declare a victim and a killer -
...他们的名字 被刻在一个木球上
their name is embedded in grain of wood.
因为每一个都是独特的 无论纹理或形状
Since each piece is unique, the shape and grain is unique -
...形状或纹理不可能被伪造
the shape and grain is impossible to forge.
- 我确定你也知道犯罪预警这种方式的法律缺陷 - 又来了
- I'm sure you all understand the legalistic drawback to precrime methodology. - Here we go again.
你看 我不代表 ACLU(美国公民自由协会) 杰夫
Look, I'm not with the ACLU on this, Jeff.
我们不要骗自己了 我们逮捕的只是并未犯法的人
But let's not kid ourselves, we are arresting individuals who're broken no law.
但他们即将犯法
But they will.
罪案本身是注定会发生的  预言师可以看到未来
The commission of the crime itself is absolute metaphysics.
他们从未失手
The Precogs see the future. And they're never wrong.
案件还没发生就被阻止  这算什么罪案
But it's not the future if you stop it.
这难道不是自相矛盾吗?
Isn't that a fundamental paradox?
是的
Yes, it is.
你在谈论预知条件 这总是在发生
You're talking about predetermination, which happens all the time.
- 为什么你抓住它? - 因为它要掉了
- Why did you catch that? - Because it was going to fall.
- 你确定? - 是的
- You're certain? - Yeah.
但是它没有掉 你抓住了它
But it didn't fall. You caught it.
你阻止过一件事的发生  并不等于同样的事就不会再发生
The fact that you prevented it from happening doesn't change the fact that it was going to happen.
你遇到过错误的例证吗?
You ever get any false positives?
有人想杀他的妻子或者老板 但他们从来没有付诸实施过
Someone intends to kill his boss or his wife, but they never go through with it.
预言师怎么区别其中不同呢?
How do the Precogs tell the difference?
预言师看不到你倾向于干什么 只能看到你将要干什么
The Precogs don't see what you intend to do, only what you will do.
那为什么他们不能预言到强奸、袭击或者自杀
Then why can't they see rapes, or assaults or suicides?
因为谋杀的本质
Because of the nature of murder.
是再没有比见到人类被她的同类谋杀
"There's nothing more destructive to the metaphysical fabric" -
更让人精神痛苦的事了
"that binds us than the untimely murder of one human being by another".
不知为什么 我不认为那是沃尔特·惠特曼
Somehow, I don't think that was Walt Whitman.
是艾丽思·海因曼
It was Iris Hineman.
她发明了犯罪预警系统 设计了系统的最初界面
She developed the Precogs, designed the system and pioneered the interface.
- 顺便说一句 我很乐意打个招呼 - 和海因曼?
- Speaking of interfacing, I'd love to say hello. - To Hineman?
和他们
To them.
上头有命令不允许进入神殿
Cops aren't allowed inside the temple.
真的吗? 你从来都没有进去过?
Really? You're never been inside?
我们遵循严格的隔离程序 以防止任何人被误判
We keep a strict separation so that no one can be accused of tampering.
那我就是第一个进去的人了?
So I'll be the first one to go in then?
- 或许你没有在听我说 - 是否授权存在问题?
- Maybe you didn't hear me. - If it's a question of authority.
- 没有问题 你没有任何授权 - 我口袋里的许可证说的可不一样
- There is no question. You don't have any. - I have a warrant in my pocket that says different.
- 给我看看 - 当然
- Show it to me. - Sure.
这次对于犯罪预防部及其人员的调查
This investigation of Precrime and it's personnel.
直接由美国政府司法部长
Has been conducted under the direct supervision, -
特别许可及监管
and express permission from the Attorney General of the United States.
我作为他的代表来这
I'm here as his representative.
那就意味着... 你的行动将受我监管
Which means... you're now operating under my supervision.
看来你很困惑 约翰
It seems you've been left out of the loop, John.
好了 我们准备好了 走吧
Alright we are ready. Let's go.
在这等一下
Alright there. Hold it.
"未许可入内"
"Not cleared for access."
"识别 约翰·安德顿允许进入"
"Ident. John Anderton approved for entry."
- 华利! - 不 不行...
- Wally! - No no no no no...
没关系 这是丹尼·维特沃 他从司法部来 我们带他了解一下情况
It's okay. This is Danny Witwer. He's from Justice and we're to give him a run of the farm.
- 我不能碰你 - 别碰他 或这里的任何东西
- I can't touch you! - Don't touch him, or anything else in here.
- 约翰 你不能进这 - 我知道
- And John, you can't be in here! - I understand.
你只需要回答他的问题 然后我们就会离开
Just answer his questions and we will get the hell outta here.
- 请告诉我... - 嘘! 他们在睡觉
- Tell me how... - Shhh! They're sleeping.
抱歉 能告诉我 这一切都是怎么运作的吗?
Sorry. Tell me how all this works.
光子乳液提供给他们 营养和液体介质
The photon milk acts as both a nutrient supply and a liquid conductor.
那可以增强他们接收的图像
It enhances the images that each of them receive.
那个女人的叫阿加莎 那对双胞胎是阿瑟和丹谢尔
We call the female Agatha. The twins are Arthur and Dashiell.
我们对他们进行眼部X光断层扫瞄
We scan by way of optical tomography.
白光细微脉冲沿着他们的头夹传播
White light pinpoints pulse along the entire length of the headgear -
并且在被大脑组织吸收了以后 被重新收集整理
and are re-read after absorption through their brain tissue.
换句话说 我们就能看到他们看到的
In other words, we see what they see.
他们不会感到任何痛苦 我们必须把睡眠剂小心控制在某个水平
They don't feel any pain. We keep their heads pretty well stocked with dopamine and endorphins.
否则他们会沉睡不醒
Plus, we maintain careful control over their serotonin levels.
他们也不能太清醒
Don't want them to drift off to sleep, but they can't be kept too awake either.
你最好别把他们当成人类看待
It's better if you don'nt think of them as human.
不...比之更甚
No... they're much more than that.
科学已经带走了我们大部分的奇迹
Science has stolen most of our miracles.
在某种意义上说他们给我们希望... 希望神力的存在
In a way they give us hope... hope of the existence of the divine.
我觉得有趣的是 有人把预测师奉若神明
I find it interesting that some people have begun to deify the Precogs.
预测师只是经过 模式筛选之后的产物 仅此而已
The Precogs are pattern recognition filters, that's all.
- 是的 但是你称这里为"神殿" - 只是一个绰号
- Yeah. But you call this room "the temple". - Just a nickname.
神谕就是所有的力量 神力总是来源与牧师
The oracle isn't where the power is anyway. The power's always been with the priests.
即使他们不得不创造神谕
Even if they had to invent the oracle.
你们这些家伙点头 就好像你们知道他在说什么似的
You guys are nodding like you actually know what the hell he's talking about.
好吧 长官 我看 我们这些改变命运的行为...
Well. come on, Chief, the way we were changing destiny and all -
我的意思是... 我们不像执法者倒更像僧侣
- I mean... we're more like clergy than cops.
- 杰德? - 什么?
- Jad? - Yeah?
回去工作 所有人
Go to work. All of you.
对不起 老毛病
Sorry. Old habit.
我在没当警察前 在富勒神学院学习过三年
I spent three years at Fuller Seminary before I became a cop.
- 我的父亲非常自豪 - 他对你的择职思路怎么看?
- My father was very proud. - What does he think of your chosen line of work?
我不知道 他在我十五岁时 在去都柏林我们的教堂的路上被枪杀了
I don't know. He was shot and killed when I was fifteen on the steps of our church in Dublin.
我知道失去自己最亲近的人 是怎样的感觉 约翰
I know what it's like to lose someone close, John.
当然 没有什么能像 失去自己的孩子那样痛苦
Of course, nothing is like the loss of a child.
我没有孩子 所以我只能想像那是什么感觉
I don't have any children of my own, so I can only imagine what that must have been like.
在众目下自己的独生子被掳
To lose your son in such a public place like that.
至少现在我们有机会 确保这种事不再发生...
At least now you and I have the chance to make sure that kind of thing doesn't happen to anyone...
为什么你不停止你那虚伪的表演 丹尼 然后告诉我你究竟想找什么?
Why don't you cut the cute act, Danny, and tell me exactly what it is you're looking for?
缺陷
Flaws.
六年里没有一宗谋杀案 系统没有任何错误 这...
There hasn't been a murder in six years. There's nothing wrong with the system. It is...
很完美 我同意
Perfect, I agree.
如果它有缺陷 他们都是人 他们一直都是
If there's a flaw, it's human. It always is.
华利
Wally!
你看到了吗?
Can you see?
约翰 见鬼 出什么事了?
John, what the hell just happened?
她的肾上腺激素水平已经降到底了! 你对她做了什么?
Her ACTH levels just shot through the roof! What did you do to her?
她突然抓住了我
She grabbed me.
抓住你? 这不可能 预言师甚至不可能察觉到我们
Grabbed you? It's impossible. The Precogs aren't even aware of us.
- 在乳液里他们所能看到的只有未来 - 她直直的瞪着我
- In the milk all they see is the future. - She looked straight at me.
可能是个恶梦 有时他们会梦见以前的谋杀案
Could have been a nightmare. Sometimes they dream about the old murders.
- 她和我说话 - 和你? 她说了什么?
- She spoke to me. - To you? What did she say?
"你看到了吗? "
"Can you see?"
你是门卫?
You the sentry?
是的 先生 我是基德
Yes, sir. I'm Gideon.
你是安德顿长官
You're Chief Anderton.
音乐是用来安抚犯人情绪的
The music relaxes the prisoners.
我从来没见过犯罪预防部的人来过 我没有麻烦吧?
I don't ever see any of you precops down here, I'm not in trouble am I?
没有 我只是对一个凶手感兴趣
Not yet. I'm interested in a murder.
- 我这关了许多 什么类型? - 溺毙
- I got plenty of those. Kill type? - Drowning.
这种手段很少见 这种凶手不多
That narrows it down. Not too many in here for that one.
受害人是高加索白人
Victim's Caucasian female.
有关司法部吗?
This about the Justice Department?
我被告知明天要穿着整齐 接待他们审查
I'm supposed to spruce up for a tour the got planned for tomorrow.
告诉我要打领带 你喜欢这东西吗?
Told me to wear a tie. You like this one?
停!
Stop!
倒回去
Roll back.
那里!
There!
她这个案子可是很早了 最早的案件之一
She's a golden oldie. One of our first.
可能是在你来之前就有了
Probably before your time.
- 这是三个预测师预测的官方合成记录吗? - 是啊
- This is the official composite of the three Precogs? - That's right.
资料影像全部基于他们三个预测镜象
Combined data stream based on all three previsions.
只显示给我阿加莎的预测镜像
Just show me Agatha's data stream.
这样啊
For that.
我们来趟旅行吧
We go for a ride.
我的上帝
My God.
我已经忘了这有这么多
I have forgotten there were so many.
你想想 如果没有你们 他们在外面都会杀人
And to think they're all be out there killing people if it wasn't for you.
看看他们 看上去多么平和
Look at them. Look at how peaceful they all seam.
但是内心却狂躁不安
But on the inside: Busy, busy, busy.
哦 这个 这是个坏蛋
Okee pokee. Now that is one bad man.
他把一个叫安妮·莱夫利的女人 淹死在罗兰湖里
He drowned a woman named Anne Lively out at Roland Lake.
凶手是个无名氏 没有身份识别
The killer is a John Doe. Never identified.
为什么他的身份不能确定? 不能进行眼部扫瞄辨认吗?
Why is he still a John Doe? Why wasn'nt he ever ID's from the EYEscan?
问题在于那不是他的眼睛
On account of those are not his eyes.
他换了眼睛想蒙骗识别器
He had them swapped out to fool the scanners.
现在街上花几千块就能办到
You get it done on the street for a few thousand bucks these days.
- 好吧 那么你只想要 那个女人看到的影像 - 是的
- Okay, so you want just the female prevision. - That's right.
- 我们看来没有她的镜像 - 再试试
- We don't seem to have her data. - Try again.
真是奇怪
This is odd.
你看 我们有两个预知镜像
See. We have the two previsions.
阿瑟的和丹谢尔的
We got what Art saw, we got what Dash saw.
但是阿加莎的不在这
But Agatha's isn't here.
可能只是个小故障
Probably just a glitch.
告诉我有关受害人的事 那个安妮·莱夫利
Tell me about the intended victim. This Anne Lively.
看起来她是个瘾君子 就像那个无名氏
Looks like she was a neuroin addict like our John Doe here, -
但是我这有条历史记录 显示她的戒毒所地址
- but I show an address history that includes the Beaton Clinic.
那就是说她戒毒了 那她现在在哪?
So she cleaned up. Where is she now?
我猜又出故障了
I guess glitches come in two's.
你会发觉从一个洞里面爬出来 又掉进了另外一个洞里
You finally crawl your way out of one hole, just to fall into another.
不 我不能让你把资料带出去 长官
No. I can't let you take that out of here, Chief.
- 这是违反规定的 - 这里还有其他什么事违反规定吗?
- It's against the rules. - Anything else going on in here that's against the rules?
小心点 长官...
Careful, Chief...
你翻旧帐 只会发现它们肮脏
You dig up the past, all you get is dirty.
你说第三个镜像怎么了 类似模糊或者什么
And you say the third prevision was, what, kind of fuzzy or something?
不 是没有第三个镜像 阿加莎的镜像不在里面
No, no the third prevision, Agatha's prevision, wasn't there.
不仅如此 我在那里花时间查了 发现有十几个案件的镜像都不完整
That's not all. I spent a few hours down there and there's a dozen more cases with missing previsions.
- 我还以为我们找到治疗感冒的方法了呢 - 该吃药了
- You're think we're have found a cure for the common cold by now. - It's stress.
- 这是什么? - 加蜂蜜的草药茶
- What's this? - Herbal tea with honey.
我讨厌草药茶...也讨厌蜂蜜
I hate herbal tea...almost as much as I hate honey.
在我把它倒在你大腿上之前 你最好喝了它
Just drink it before I pour it in your lap.
- 你需要点什么吗 约翰? - 不 谢谢
- Can I get you anything, John? - No, thank you.
维沃特计划明天去监守室查看
Witwer is scheduled for a Containment... tour of Containment tomorrow.
好啊 带他去吧
Yeah, give him a tour.
- 拉拉打了电话给我 - 什么?
- Lara called me. - What?
- 她很担心你 坦白的说 我也是 - 我很好
- She's worried about you. And, quite frankly, so am I. - I'm fine.
我明白你把大部分时间放在工作上
I understand you're been spending a lot of time in the sprawl.
- 我去过那里 - 在午夜?
- I go running down there. - In the middle of the night?
如果丹尼·维沃特 现在对你进行药理检查怎么办?
What if Danny Witwer came to you right now and insisted on a full chem run?
拉马 我很好
Lamar, I'm fine.
你知道的 约翰 一旦犯罪预防计划推向全国 他们就阻止不了我们
You understand, John, the minute Precrime goes national, they're going to take it away from us.
我们不会让他们得逞
We won't let them.
不会? 一个老男人和一个被开除的警察怎么对抗他们?
No? How's an old man and a cop on the whiff ever going to stop them?
我父亲曾经对我说: "不是你选择信仰 而是信仰选择你"
My father once said to me: "You don't choose the things you believe in, they choose you".
那就是你为什么在这的原因
There's a reason you're here, John.
如果犯罪预警机制早上马六个月...
Had Precrime been in place just six months earlier, -
...你和拉拉的痛苦就可以避免
- the loss you and Lara suffered would have been prevented.
记住那些眼睛 约翰...
Remember the eyes, John...
人民的眼睛正在看着我们
The eyes of the nation are on us right now.
我们都知道我的话已经没有人听
We both know Im not the generation anyone listens to.
但是 人们相信你 约翰
But, people trust you, John.
只要你说绝对信任犯罪预防系统...
When you speak of your absolute belief in Precrime, -
...让他们明白这是在痛苦和无政治因素下诞生的信仰 我很了解这个
- they know it's a belief born of pain and not politics. I've always understood that.
我也很鼓励这种原因的信仰
And I may have even encouraged it, to help with the cause.
但是现在... 你的痛苦伤害了我们两个
But now... your pain is hurting both of us.
他们不能把这一切从我们身边夺走
They're not going to take it away from us.
我不会允许的
I won't let them.
命中!
Bingo!
- "嘿 爸爸" - "你好啊 小朋友"
- "Hi, daddy!" - "Hello little buddy."
- "我们成立了一个俱乐部" - "是吗? "
- "I made up a club." - "Yeah?"
- "我们叫它帕莱斯高"
- "We'll call it 'The Crushcoes."
- "我们有一个足球队" - "真的? "
- "We made up a soccer team." - "Yeah?"
- "我们在学校练习" - "是吗? 你们练习的好吗..."
- "And we practiced at school." - "Yeah? You did you practice for..."
爸爸有很多麻烦了 肖恩
Daddy's in a lot of trouble, Sean.
- 杰德 为什么你没有和维沃特神父在一起? - 你不该这么情绪化
- Jad. How come you're not out there with Father Witwer? - We're in motion on something.
根据我看到的情况 受害者 白人 男性 大约50岁 身高1.70左右
From what I can see, we got a white male-victim, about five-ten, approximately one-seventy, -
...在十搂被枪击 然后掉出窗外
- takes a round in the ten ring, and goes out a window.
- 红球? - 不是 棕球
- Red Ball? - Nope. Brown ball.
这个是有预谋的
This one is premeditated.
令人惊讶的是在方圆200英里以内 居然还有人敢预谋杀人
Amazing there's someone within two hundred miles actually dumb enough to still do that.
受害者叫里奥·克罗 这是1109号案 案发时间 星期五下午3:06
The victim's name is Leo Crow. This is case #1109. Time of occurrence, Friday 15.06 hours.
开始定位搜索 寻找未来受害人里奥·克罗
Start a location run and a contact search for future victim Leo Crow.
1109号案件 根据预测师提供的镜像
Case #1109, previsualized by the Precogs and recorded on holosphere by Precrime's q-stacks.
1109号案的鉴定人是凯塞琳·詹姆斯博士 和审判长弗兰克·保罗德
My fellow witnesses for case #1109 are Dr. Katherine James and Chief Justice Frank Pollard.
- 早上好 - 早上好
- Good morning. - Good morning.
鉴定人准备观看并鉴定1109号案件了吗?
Are the witnesses ready to preview and validate #1109?
- 你准备好了就行 约翰 - 开始吧
- Ready when you are, John. - Standing by.
哦 我喜欢这部分
Oh. I love this part.
我找不到地址或者其他什么 从五年前就没有记载了
I've got no address last known or otherwise, no tax returns for the last five years.
去查查NCIC 他们也许有记录
Check NCIC, maybe he's got a record.
一找到案发地点马上派行动队过去
Then send a protection team as soon as we lock location.
看上去像联邦政府大楼 混凝土 玻璃 板条格天花板
- Looks like federal housing. Concrete, glass, eggcrates.
天那 这个区至少有上千座这种楼房
Ouch. There's a thousand of those in the District.
碎片图像传入
Fractured images coming in
数字...
Numbers...
9和6
Nine and six.
女性 老人 她在抽烟...烟斗
Female. Senior. She's smoking a...pipe.
她在笑
She's laughing.
好啦 现在进到一个房间
Okay. Now inside a room.
窗玻璃 映出人影
Windowpanes, illumine exclusion.
两个不太清晰的人影?
What two figures resolving in the room?
看来我们有个第三者
Looks like we got a third party.
戴着太阳眼镜 在窗外
Wearing sunglasses just out the window...
你不会杀我的
You're not gonna kill me.
再见 克罗
Good-bye, Crow.
"你不会杀了我的"
"You're not gonna kill me."
- "再见 克罗" - "安德顿 等一下"
- "Good-bye, Crow." - "Anderton! Wait!"
- 你说了什么 长官? - 没有
- You say something, Chief? - No.
我来拿这个
I'll get this one.
我们有充足的时间办这案子 杰德
We got time on this one, Jad.
不介意下楼去帮我买份蛋糕吧 我饿坏了
Mind going down getting me a piece of that cake they're eating down there? I'm starving.
- 当然 长官 顺便也可以为我自己买一份 - 不着急
- Sure, Chief. I think I'll get one for myself while I'm at it. - Take your time.
安德顿长官 我看到了什么?
Chief Anderton. What is this that I...see?
我很困惑...
I'm confused about...
- "安德顿 等一下" - "再见 克罗"
- "Anderton. Wait!" - "Good-bye, Crow."
"等一下 安德顿 等一下"
"Wait! Anderton. Wait!"
"安德顿 等一下"
"Anderton. Wait!"
我喜欢你 长官
I like you, Chief.
你对我一直很好
You're always been nice to me.
在我拉响警报前 我会给你两分钟时间
I'll give you two minutes before I hit the alarm.
请等一下 谢谢
Hold that, please. Thanks.
你有大麻烦了 约翰
You're in a lot of trouble, John.
你陷害我...
You set me up...
我在报告里面提到了你有妄想症 你整夜吸毒
I'll write the paranoia off to the whiff you've been doping on all night.
- 放松点 - 看起来我找到缺陷了
- Easy. - It seems I've found a flaw.
你想干什么
What are you gonna do?
单就这件事你就要坐六个月牢 更别提你的证章了
Possession alone will cost you six months, not to mention your badge.
我猜我们不能一起工作了
I guess we won't be working together after all.
现在放下枪 我可不希望听说又有红球事件
Now put the gun down, John. I don't hear a Red Ball.
拉马! 拉马!
Lamar! Lamar!
- 拉马! - 约翰 出什么事了?
- Lamar! - John. What the hell is happening?
- 维沃特陷害我 - 到底怎么了?
- It's Witwer he set me up! - What the hell is happening?
- 他陷害我 - 约翰 等等...谁?
- He set me up! - John, just wait...who...?
- 他陷害我 维沃特 是维沃特 他... - 是吗? 谁是受害者?
- He set me up! Witwer it's Witwer! He... - Yeah, who's the victim?
- 某人 - 谁?
- Somebody. - Who?
- 某人...里奥·克罗 - 那是谁?
- Someone...Leo Crow. - Who is he?
我不知道 从来没听说过
I have no idea. I've never heard of him.
但我被认为不到36个小时之后会杀了他
But I'm supposed to kill him in less than 36 hours.
- 维沃特怎么能进入系统呢? - 他假造了输出信号
- How could Witwer have accessed the case file? - He faked his cerebral output.
- 为什么不是别人呢? - 你觉得呢?
- Why would anyone want to? - Can you?
- 我很怀疑这一点 - 但是...海因曼知道原因吗?
- But I doubt it very much. - But would...would Hineman know?
- 过来吧 - 什么?
- Come in. - What?
- 我们会保护你的安全 直到这件事被查清楚 - 不 不 不
- Well I'll keep you safe until we get to the bottom of this. - No no no.
拉马 听我说 听着 和华利谈谈 看看维沃特有没有又进过神殿
Lamar, listen to me, listen, talk to Wally, see if Witwer's gone inside the temple again.
问问杰德有关下班时间的门禁系统里眼部扫瞄的记录
Then ask Jad for any off hour EYEdents into the analytical room.
约翰 告诉我 谁是里奥·克罗
John. Just tell me, who's Leo Crow?
一级安全防范激活
Security lockdown enabled.
修正目的地:办公室
Revised Destination: Office.
拉马 他们发现我了
Lamar, they have found me.
- 有什么办法解除锁定吗? 约翰? - 没有
- Is there any way to override the lockdown? John? - No, no.
- 没有 - 没有?
- No. - No?
你定个地方  我们在那里碰面
I'll meet you anywhere you say.
- 拉马 - 你可以来我家 约翰
- Lamar. - You can come to my house, John.
不行 我会在那里被抓  我不要戴头铐
You know I can't. They'll get me. I'm not gonna get halo.
你不能逃跑 约翰
You can't run, John.
是人都会逃
Everybody runs.
-天啊  -喂  喂
Oh, my God!  Hey, hey.
老天 你还好吗?
Oh, my gosh. Are you okay?
别担心 先生 我会把他平安带回来的
Don't worry, sir. I'll bring him in unharmed.
事实上 戈登 你不必这样做的
Actually, Gordon, you're not gonna do that.
- 我来接管队伍 - 什么?
- I'm taking control of the team. - What?
维沃特 弗雷彻是副队长 这是他负责的
Witwer, Fletcher is second in command. It's his show to run.
如果你想 你可以监督
If you want, you can observe.
- 去吧 找到他 - 是的 先生
- Do it. Find him. - Yes, sir.
就在这事发生前几天 他来找过你 说了些什么?
He came to see you the other day right before he was tagged.
你们说了什么?
What did you talk about?
职棒 他们今年投手群不强
The Mets. John doesn't think they're got a deep enough pitching roster this year, -
而我认为...
and I'm inclined to...
你为什么要维护他?
Why are you protecting him?
你早就知道他吸毒 你没有采取任何措施
You knew he was doping, yet you did nothing about it.
- 他失去了孩子 看在上帝的份上... - 都六年了
- The man lost a child, for Christ's sake... - Six years ago.
- 你们两个说了什么? - 和你见鬼的任务无关
- What did you two talk about? - None of your damn business.
现在 所有这些 都和我的见鬼任务有关 拉马
Oh, it's all my damn business now, Lamar.
我负责调查与监控严重罪案
Investigation of a supervising office for a capital crime falls under federal jurisdiction, -
防止任何共谋的可能性发生 他是我的嫌疑犯
- so as to rule out any possibility of conspiracy. He's my suspect.
- 他是我的下属 - 我们给司法部长打个电话如何?
- He's my subordinate! - Shall we call the Attorney General?
我想他会很乐意给你澄清问题
I'm sure he'll be happy to clarify the issue for you.
我不希望约翰·安德顿受伤害
I don't want John Anderton hurt.
我会喜欢在这工作的
I'm gonna enjoy working here.
"通往沙漠边缘之路...莱克撒斯"
"A road to verges in the desert...Lexus."
"约翰·安德顿 你不想来一次小旅行吗? "
"The road your on, John Anderton, is the one less travel..."
"晚上好 约翰·安德顿"
"Good evening, John Anderton..."
"约翰·安德顿"
"John Anderton!"
"你可以现在享受一大瓶啤酒"
"You can use a Guinness Draught by now..."
"从所有的问题中解脱出来"
"Escape from it all".
"摆脱压力 约翰·安德顿"
"Stress out, John Anderton."
"逃开吧 约翰·安德顿"
"Get away. John Anderton."
"忘记你的烦恼"
"Forget your troubles..."
在伦敦地下车站发现他了
He's been idented on the Metro.
地铁停两个站 在28、33街
The train makes two stops, at 20th and then 33rd.
两站都派出人手
Send units, siege location.
- 20街来不及了 - 自信点
- They'll never make 20th. - Have faith.
（新闻快报）
（犯罪预防中心抓捕自己人）
启动喷射背心
Fire 'em up!
- 你好 弗雷彻 - 你好 约翰
- Hey Fletch. - Hey John.
- 很糟的着陆 - 是的
- That was a rough landing. - Yeah.
-你需要多练习 -我的膝盖不太好
-You have to work on that. -It's the shit knee of mine.
别这样
Don't do it.
嘿 别这样干
Hey, don't do this.
约翰 不要逃跑
John. Don't run.
你不一定要追我
You don't have to chase me.
你不一定要跑
You don't have to run.
每个人都会逃跑 弗雷彻
Everybody runs, Fletch.
你知道我们会抓住你
You know we'll catch you.
每个人都会逃跑
Everybody runs.
- 你大可不必这样 约翰 - 每个人都会逃跑
- It doesn't have to be like this, John. - Everybody runs.
准备好武器
Get your sick-sticks ready.
每个人都会跑 弗雷彻
Everybody runs, Fletch.
过来 长官 放松点
Slow down, Chief. Just take it easy.
别轻举妄动 长官
No sudden moves, Chief.
约翰 这没什么的
John. It's okay.
- 弗雷彻 - 放松点 长官
- Fletch. - Easy does it, Chief.
- 抓紧了吗? 抓紧了吗? - 是的
- Got a grip? Got a grip?! - Yeah.
长官 长官
Chief. Chief. Chief!
安德顿!
Anderton!
滚出去! 滚出我的厨房!
Go away! Get out of my kitchen!
- 安德顿! 收手吧 - 把他从我身上拉下来 弗雷彻 把他拉下来!
- Anderton! Stop! - Pull him off me, Fletcher. Get him off me!
遵照哥伦比亚特区犯罪预防部的命令 我拘捕你...
By mandate of the District of Columbia Precrime division, I'm placing you under arrest...
睡吧
Go to sleep.
你们跟我来!
You stay with me!
- 海因曼博士 - 你随便闯入 我不接待来访者
- Dr. Hineman. - You're trespassing I don't have visitors.
恐怕这是娃娃眼造成的
Oh, I'm afraid that would be from the Doll's Eye.
那些藤蔓...在擦破皮肤时注入毒液 因为你未经许可翻我的围墙
The vine...the Baneberry that scratched you during your illegal climb over my wall...
虽然不是纯种娃娃眼 是我培育的杂交品种
It's not a true Doll's Eye, of course, but a little hybrid of my own design.
它们不同寻常 一旦毒素进入你的血液
It's quite something, once the poison gets into your bloodstream, -
你就会看见那些 我称之为
you'll start to see what I can only describe as
让人沮丧的事物的特别展览
the most extraordinary display of blue objects.
这不是你想要的对吗?
This just isn't your week, is it...
安德顿长官
Chief Anderton.
我不是凶手
I'm not a killer.
你最好喝了这个
You better drink this.
很快你就不能吞咽东西了
Soon you won't be able to swallow, and then you'll be totally buggered.
全喝了
All of it.
好了 现在稍微休息调整一下 会好的
Okay. Now take a minute to right yourself.
刚才... 你认为我能帮你什么?
Just...what is it you think I can do for you?
你能告诉我...
You can tell me how someone...
如何能伪造预知镜像吗?
Can fake a prevision.
我怎么会知道?
How would I know that?
因为你发明了这个系统
Because you invented Precrime.
这很好笑吗?
What's so funny?
这是一系列基因工程错误引起的
If the unintended consequences of a series of genetic mistakes -
加上科学上的失误
and science gone haywire
也能被称为发明 是的 是我发明的
can be called invention, yes, then I invented Precrime.
你看上去不怎么自豪
You don't seem all that proud.
一点都不  我是要修复他们  不是把他们变成别的
I'm not. I was trying to heal them, not turn them into something else.
修复谁?
Heal who?
那些阻止罪犯的人
The innocents we now use to stop the guilty.
你是在说...
You're talking about...
预言师...
the Precogs...
你以为水箱里那三个人 是试管培养出来的吗?
You think the three in the tank come out of a test tube?
他们仅仅是幸存者
They are merely the ones who survived.
我当时在伍德海文诊所 治疗那些吸毒成瘾的孩子
I was doing genetic research at the Woodhaven Clinic treating children of drug addicts.
十年前烈洛因第一次在大街上出现时
This was ten years ago when neuroin at first hit the streets.
那是一种不纯的毒品 不是基因工程鸡尾酒
It was an empure form of the drug not the engineered cocktail, -
在受过高等教育的人群里非常流行
that became so popular among the more educated.
那些孩子从一出生大脑就受到毒品的严重伤害 大多在12岁前就死了
All of these kids where born with severe brain damage. Most died before the age of twelve.
幸存者很少 这些幸存的孩子很珍贵 他们有一种天赋
There was few, there was precious few who survived, they had a gift.
我称之为天赋 但其实更像上帝在开玩笑
I called it a gift for them it was more like a cosmic joke.
他们会在夜里醒来
They would wake up in the night.
蜷在房间的一角 尖叫 紧紧靠着墙壁
Curled up in a corner of the room, screaming, clunging at the wallpaper.
因为当这些孩子在夜里一闭上眼睛
Because when these little children, you see, closed their eyes at night.
他们不停的梦到凶杀 一个接着一个
They dreamt only of murder over and over, one after the other.
没有过多久我们就意识到...
And it didn't take long for us to realize, -
那些被称为噩梦的场景...
that the real nightmare was that these so-called dreams -
实际上过不了多久就真实发生了
were about to come true these murders were actually happening.
你是说有些孩子死了?
You say some of the children died?
无论我们怎么治疗  他们大多没活下来  或许他们是因治疗而死
So many of them despite what we did for them. Or maybe because of what we did to them.
但无所谓了 现在这是个完美的系统 不是吗?
But it doesn't matter. It's a perfect system now, isn't it?
我不会犯谋杀罪的
I'm not gonna commit murder.
我根本不认识那个人  又怎么会去杀他
I've never even met the man I'll supposed to kill.
但是 事情已经开始了 一条线索会引导你最终去杀掉他
And, yet, a chain of events has started. A chain that will lead you inexorably to his murder.
- 如果我避而不见他呢? - 你怎么躲过一个你从来没见过的人?
- Not if I stay away from him. - How can you avoid a man you're never met?
那么说你不会帮我了?
So you won't help me?
我无能为力 没有人可以帮你 预言师从来没有失误过
I can't help you. Nobody can. The Precogs are never wrong.
但是 偶尔...
But, occasionally,
...他们的预言不一致
they do disagree.
什么?
What?
大部分时候 三个预言师会看到同样的事件
Most of the time, all three Precognitives will see an event in the same way.
但是偶尔 他们其中的一个看到的镜像 是不同于其他两个人的
But once in a while, one of them will see things differently than the other two.
天哪!
Jesus Christ.
为什么我从不知道?
Why didn't I know about this?
- 因为这些少数派报告一出现就会被删除 - 为什么?
- Because these Minority Reports are destroyed the instant they occur. - Why?
很明显 做为犯罪预防来说 是不允许有任何不可靠信息的
Obviously, for Precrime to function, there can't be any suggestion of fallibility.
毕竟 在一个公正的系统里注入怀疑有什么好处呢?
After all, what good is a Justice system that instills doubt?
或许是有道理 但是这还是值得怀疑的
It may be reasonable, but it's still doubt.
你是说我冤枉了好人?
Are you saying that I've haloll innocent people?
我是说有那么多被指控为未来犯罪的人...
I'm saying that every so often those accused of a precrime might, -
只是可能 但或许他们有一个不同的未来
just might, have an alternate future.
伯吉斯知道这事吗? 关于这个少数派报告?
Does Burgess know about this? About this Minority Report?
我常常和拉马开玩笑 说我们是犯罪预防部的父亲和母亲
I used to joke with Lamar that we were the mother and father of Precrime.
通常父母眼中的孩子未必总和实际情况一样...
Well, in my experience, parents very often see their children as they want them to be, not as they are...
回答我 拉马·伯吉斯知道少数派报告吗?
Answer my question. Does Lamar Burgess know about the Minority Report?
当然知道 但是我们都觉得 这种报告是无足轻重的
Yes, of course, he knew, but at the time, he felt, we both felt their existence was an insignificant variable.
对你来说或许无足轻重 但是那些被我抓走的人呢? 他们的未来呢?
Insignificant to you maybe, but what about those people I put away with alternate futures?
- 老天  如果人们知道有这种失误... - 这个系统就完了
- My God, if the country knew there was a chance... - The system would collapse.
- 我信任这个系统... - 真的吗?
- I believe in that system... - Do you really?
你想毁灭它
You wanna bring it down.
你会毁灭它...
You will bring it down,
...如果你想杀了你的受害者
if you manage to kill your victim.
你当然想杀 这就会成为证明犯罪预警系统无效的证据
Why, that will be the most spectacular public display of how Precrime...didn't work.
- 我不会杀任何人 - 秉持这个信念吧
- I'm not gonna kill anybody. - Hold that thought.
为什么我要信任你?
Why should I trust you?
你没必要 你没必要相信任何人...
You shouldn't. You shouldn't trust anyone... -
...也不要相信那个自以为是的司法部长
- certainly not the Attorney General who just wants it all for himself.
或是那个想砸你饭碗的年轻联邦探员
Not the young federal agent who wants your job.
甚至是那个只会炫耀自己创造成果的老头 不要相信任何人
Not even the old man who just wants to hang onto what he has created. Don't trust anyone.
去找少数派报告
Just find the Minority Report.
但你说少数派报告已经被销毁了
You said the Minority Report was destroyed.
记录是销毁了 但是原本的报告还在
The record is destroyed. The original report still exists.
无论何时 一旦一个报告生成 我设计的系统...
I designed the system so that whenever a report occurred, -
会把它存在一个安全的地方而不会被销毁
- it would be stored in a safe place but not declared.
什么安全的地方?
What safe place is that?
- 安全的地方是在... - 在哪?
- The safest place there is... - Where is it?
在生成幻象的预言师的身体里
Inside the Precog who predicted it.
你所要做的就是把它们下载下来 亲爱的
All you have to do is download it, darling.
就这样 嗯?
That's all, huh?
只需要想办法混进犯罪预防部 进入神殿 接触预言师
Just walk right into Precrime, get into the Temple, somehow tap into these Precogs, -
- 然后下载少数派报告... - 如果你运气好的话
- and then download this Minority Report... - If you have one.
然后走出来
And then walk out.
事实上 我认为你应该跑出来  这就是你要做的
Actually, I think you'll have to run out, but yes, that is what you have to do.
你疯了 你以为我是谁?
You're insane or you think I am.
早在我靠近犯罪预防部十英里的范围之前 就会受到无数次眼部扫瞄
I'll get EYEscanned a dozen times before I get within ten miles of Precrime.
有时候为了看到光明 你必须先冒险进入黑暗
Sometimes in order to see the light, you have to risk the dark.
作为一名警察...请原谅 曾经是一名警察
As a policeman...excuse me, a former policeman -
我确信你能找到 所有在这方面能帮的上你的人
- I'm sure you know all sorts of people who could help you out in this regard.
有趣的是所有的有机生物都很相似
It's funny how all living organisms are alike.
当威胁到来 危及自身的时候
When the chips are down. When the pressure is on.
地球上的每种生物就只关心一件事 那就是:
Every creature on the face of the Earth is interested in one thing and one thing only:
他们自己的生存
It's own survival.
去找少数派报告吧
Find the Minority Report.
我怎么知道谁有那个报告?
How do I even know which one has it?
它通常都在他们最有天分的那个人身上
It's always in the more gifted of the three.
是谁?
Which one is that?
那个女孩
The female.
我们再看看这
Alright here's where we're at.
房间里有三个人 受害者在这
Three men in a room. The victim is here.
约翰在这
John is here.
这个身份不明的男子在窗外
And this unidentified male out the window.
对面的建筑像是政府的福利公寓 但是我还不能确定犯罪地点...
The adjacent building suggests public housing, but I can't make out the location. Which means...
这个城里有上千的类似建筑
There's thousands of units like this one.
他们可能在任何地方
They're everywhere.
但是他在22小时之内是不会去杀里奥·克罗的
But he doesn't go there to kill Crow for another twenty-two hours.
- 对不起 这是安德顿长官的位置 你不能坐他的... - 他不会再来这了
Excuse me this is Chief Anderton's space you can sit in his... - He's not here anymore.
- 他会回来的 - 我表示怀疑...
- He'll be back! - I doubt that...
你是怎么回事...?
What happened to you...?
与此同时 我打赌他现在藏在市郊某处
In the meantime, I'm betting he's somewhere in the sprawl.
安德顿很聪明 他不会去有电子广告板或者其他会暴露身份的地方
Anderton's smart enough to go where electronic billboards and other media can't ID him to pick his pocket.
市郊的消费者较少 也就意味着有较少的扫瞄器会威胁他
There's fewer consumers down there, which means fewer scanners to target him.
为什么他不干脆逃跑?
Why wouldn't he just run?
因为他认为他是清白的
Because he thinks he's innocent.
我们把精力放在市郊
We concentrate on the sprawl.
我们派两个飞行小组带着蜘蛛追踪器过去
We do overflies in ships with two spyder teams on the ground.
对整个地区进行热能扫瞄 读取每个人的眼部和心跳资料
Thermal scan the entire area, read anything with eyes and a heartbeat.
她在哪?
Where is she?
真冷
This damn cold.
别担心
Don't worry.
你看 我能切开你的胸腔 缝进一只死猫但绝对不会感染
You see. I could cut open your chest, sew a dead cat in there and you'll never get an infection.
我会给你打抗生素 防止感染
Not with the spectrum of antibios I'll be shooting into you.
那真让人感到安慰
That's comforting.
你知道我可以只给你更换新虹膜
You do understand I can't just give you new irises.
别碰那个
Please don't touch.
因为扫瞄器会发现疤痕
Because the scanners will read the new scar tissue.
警报响过以后 大批的武装警察出现
Alarms will go off and large men with guns will appear.
那是什么?
What was that?
- 止血剂 会有帮助 - 你总是这样偷偷摸摸的对你的病人吗?
- It's anesthesia. It's all gonna be downhill. - When you sneak up on you patients like that?
你不能在音乐会之前弄伤小提琴家的手啊
You wouldn't break the hand of a violinist before the concert.
摆脱 放松
Please, relax.
我所想告诉你的就是我要更换你的整个眼球
All I'm trying to tell you is that I'll have to remove your eyes completely.
我知道
I know.
- 我不得不用新的替代 - 我知道 但我希望能保留原来的
- And I'll have to replace them with new ones. - I know that, but I wanna keep the old ones.
为什么?
Why?
因为那是我妈妈给我的
Because my mother gave them to me.
它对你有影响吗? 无论如何保留第二身份没有什么坏处
What's it to you? They're no good to you on the secondary market anyway.
随你怎么说 是你出钱
Whatever you say, it's your money.
让我来介绍一下我美丽的助手 范·艾可小姐
Let me introduce my gorgeous assistant, Miss Van Eyck.
- 钱不是很多 - 那是所有我能安全使用的钱
- This is not alot of money. - That's all I could safely move.
你要给我戴什么?
What did you give me?
微笑机器 告诉你 既然你我相识一场 为什么不给你个优惠价呢?
Smile-medicin. Tell you what, since you and I go way back, why don't I just give you my Old Pal discount.
你说什么?
What do you say?
你不记得我了 对吗?
You don't remember me, do you?
- 我们认识吗? - 哦 是的 我们认识
- We know each other? - Oh, yes, we do.
在哪? 华盛顿?
From where? D.C.?
巴尔的摩 东区
Baltimore. Eastside.
- 巴尔的摩? - 是的
- Baltimore? - Yeah.
我们怎么认识的?
How do we go way back?
所罗门·P·埃迪 我是个整形外科医生
Solomon P. Eddie M.D. I was a plastic surgeon.
你记得吗?
You remember?
主治烧伤患者 特别是女患者
Specialized in burn victims. Mostly women.
- 我抓过你... - 哦 是的 就是你
- I put you away... - Oh, yeah. You did.
你拍的那些带子...
You made those tapes...
那只是些表演片断
They were performance pieces.
你对你的病人放火!
You set your patients on fire!
我把火扑灭了 只不过有些人跑的慢而已 我们换个话题吧 好吗?
I put them out. Some not as quickly as others, but let's change the subject, shall we?
未来比过去有意思多了 你不那么想吗?
The future is much more interesting than the past. Don't you think?
啊 范·艾可小姐 我猜她被你迷住了
Ah, Miss Van Eyck. I'm afraid she's already smitten.
她眼里只有你
She only has eyes for you.
约翰 我知道你在想什么
I know what you are thinking, John.
我怎么会帮你? 这么说吧 监狱图书馆占去了我太多的时间
How can I do what I do now? Well let's just say that I did spend an awful lot of time in the prison library.
现在有了很多种避免监狱生活 枯燥无聊的好方法
Now that was a great way to avoid some of the more unpleasant aspects of prison life.
监狱生活是一种学习的手段 一种真正...
Confinement was a real education, a real...
大开眼界的办法
...eye opener.
你想真正受到启发...
I mean, for true enlightenment, there's nothing quite like, well let's say,
...就像当洗澡时 一个凶神恶煞对你不客气
...taking a shower while a large felon with an attitude...
你拿锤子都打不赢他  而你耳边在回响:"南希 南希..."
...you cann't even knockdown with a hammer, whispers in your ear: "Oh Nancy, oh Nancy..."
有意思 感谢你 约翰 给了我...
Now that was a lot of fun. Thank you so very much, John, for putting me...
给我机会让我更好的了解自己
Thank you so very much for giving me the opportunity to get to know myself so much better.
而现在是该报答你了...
And now to return the favour...
- 这是你的作品? - 是的
- This your work? - Yes.
我喜欢
I like it.
谢谢 你要的咖啡放点其他东西吗?
Thanks. You take anything in your coffee?
- 奶油和糖 - 抱歉 没有奶油了
- Cream and sugar. - I don't have any cream. Sorry.
- 那就放点糖吧 你和约翰来过这? - 以前是 每年夏天都来
- Just sugar then. You and John ever come here? - We used to, every summer.
他现在不在这里 是吧?
He's not here now, is he?
我必须这样问
I had to ask.
- 我连糖也没有了 - 谢谢
- You know I don't have any sugar either. - Thank you.
- 他没有试着跟你联系? - 没有
- He hasn't tried to contact you? - No.
你听他提过里奥·克罗这个名字吗?
You ever heard him mention the name Leo Crow?
没有 但是我从不和约翰谈那么远
No, but then I don't talk to John that much anymore.
- 那么你也没见过他的公寓? - 是我们的公寓
- So you haven't seen his apartment? - That was our apartment.
最近回去过吗?
Have you been there recently?
到处都是这些
It's full of these.
他吸毒多久了?
How long has he been doped?
- 自从失去我们的儿子 - 你是说他失去儿子以后
- Since right after we lost our son. - You mean after he lost your son.
谁都没错
It was nobody's fault.
但那时约翰和儿子一起在公共游池
But John was with him at the public pool.
你在你们的离婚协议书上说 约翰试图自杀
You said in your divorce papers that John tried to kill himself.
- 算不上自杀 我后悔那样说 - 什么意思?
- It wasn't a suicide attempt. I regret ever saying that. - What was it?
FBI找到了一些属于我儿子的东西
The FBI found something that belonged to my son.
一双凉鞋... 总之 约翰很不安 他...
A sandal... Anyway, John was upset. He... he...
- 他掏出枪 然后坐下来看家庭电影... - 他开了一枪...
- He took out his gun and sat down to watch his home movies... - He shot a hole...
- 拉拉 你的陈述上都写了 - 他朝该死的天花板开了一枪 那又怎样?
- It's all on your statement, Lara. - He shot a hole in the damn ceiling. So what?
你没了儿子  你会怎样？
You lose your son, let's see how well you handle it.
拉马尔说你离开约翰是因为他沉溺于预防犯罪而冷落了你
Lamar Burgess thinks that you left John because he lost himself in Precrime instead of you.
我离开他是因为每次我看着他 我就想起我的儿子
I left him because everytime I looked at him, I saw my son.
每次我接近他 我就想到我可怜的孩子
Every time I got close to him, I smelled my little boy.
所以我离开了他
That's why I left him.
现在你可以走了
And now you can leave.
12个小时内别拆绷带
Don't take the bandages off for twelve hours.
如果提前拆 你就会变瞎的 知道吗?
If you take them off before then, you'l go blind. Understand?
冰箱里有牛奶和三明治
In the fridge there is milk and sandwiches.
一定要多喝水
Make sure you drink a lot of water.
我怎么去厕所?
How do I find the bathroom?
厕所...在你的右手边
The bathroom... now that's your right hand.
厨房在左边
The kitchen is your left.
别乱摸 千万不要乱摸
Don't scratch. Never scratch!
我们都是老朋友了 我给你点赠品 也许迟早会派上用场
Seeing as we're being old pals and all, I'm gonna give you a bonus, might come in handy.
这是临时麻痹剂
This is a temporary paralytic enzyme,
- 从下巴注入你的身体 - 这是干嘛用的?
- You're gonna shoot this baby up there right under your chin. - What is this?
用来改变你的形象
All is gonna turn your pretty face into mush.
那样人们就认不出你了 知道吧
People won't even recognize you, okay.
半小时后恢复  但你会痛不欲生
In thirty minutes you're tightening up but it's gonna hurt like nothing you ever felt before.
把这个放进你的百宝箱 和你的...
Gonna put this in your goodie bag together with your...
...旧版眼珠放一起
... leftovers.
我给你定个时间 闹钟一响 就可以拆绷带了
I'm setting up a timer. When it rings tomorrow you can take off the bandages...
- 然后离开这里 但是不要提前拆 否则... - 变瞎 我知道
- and get the hell out of here. But not before then, or you'll go... - Go blind. I know.
别乱抓 这是我们的朋友送的礼物
Don't scratch! A little something from our mutual friend of ours.
12小时内别取下绷带
"Don't take the bandages off for twelve hours."
"如果提前取你就会变成瞎子 知道吧? "
"If you take them off before then, you'll go blind. Understand?"
25.16秒 一个新的记录
25.16 seconds, that's a new record.
- 是世界记录吗? - 是世界...?
- Is that a world record? - Is it a world...?
- 个人最好吧 - 好吧 我要给你计时
- It's a personal best. - Okay, then I wanna time you.
给我计时? 开玩笑吧 我根本就没可能打破25.16秒的记录
You wanna time me? You gotta be kidding. Because there is no possible way I can beat 25.16 seconds.
- 鲸鱼在水下可以屏息多久? - 大约20分钟
- How long can a whale hold its breath under water? - A whale can hold its breath for about 20 minutes.
- 那你可以打破鲸鱼的记录 - 嗯
- Then you gotta beat the whale. - Okay.
你可以打败鲸鱼...
You gotta beat the whale...
开始
Here you go.
会憋20分钟
That's gonna be 20 minutes.
- 你确定不想去要点冰淇淋还是其他的? - 不要
- You sure you don't wanna go for a ice cream or something? - No.
- 因为你知道...我会打败鲸鱼 - 是啊
- 'Cause you know...you know I'm gonna beat that whale. - Yeah.
- 把表给我 给我 - 三 二 一...开始
- Give me the count... give me the count. - Three, two, one...go!
肖恩?
Sean?
肖恩!
肖恩?
Sean!
Sean?
你看到肖...?
Have you seen...?
肖恩?
Sean?
我在找我的儿子
I'm looking for my son.
你看见一个穿红泳裤的男孩了吗?
Have you seen a boy in a red bathing suit?
肖恩!
Sean!
你看见一个穿红泳裤的男孩了...?
Have you seen a little boy in a red...
他穿着红色的泳裤
He's wearing a red bathing suit.
肖恩!
Sean!
贞德 我们已经落位 可以开始对 北鲍威尔地区的居民进行热能跟踪了
Jad, we're now in position and ready to begin thermal scan on all residents on North Powell.
弗雷彻 我觉得你肯定特别喜欢我 是吧?
I'm thinking you must really like me, don't you, Fletcher?
- 所以这回你要跟我一起行动 对吧? - 你真是自恋 克洛特
- That's why you asked to partner with me on this little sortie, isn't it? - I think you're swell company, Knott.
我和领导独处时你不信任我 这没什么
It's not at all that you don't trust me to be alone with the Chief.
你觉得 有机会我也许会干他...
That you think I might, you know, fuck with him, if I had the chance...
不 我就想看看他拿你的身体撞墙是什么样子 就这样 杰夫
No, I just wanna watch him use your body to sandblast another building. That's all. Jeff.
艾瓦娜 行动!
Evanna, go!
发现27处体热辐射
I show twenty-seven warm bodies.
收到 确定27处体热辐射
Roger that. Confirm twenty-seven warm bodies.
你觉得放4只蜘蛛如何? 一层一个?
What do you think four spyders? One per floor?
放8只吧 我还得赶时间吃东西
Let's do eight. I gotta eat.
931大楼的居民 931大楼的居民
Residents of 931 Powell. Residents of 931 Powell.
我是特区犯罪预防官弗雷彻
This is officer Fletcher D.C. Precrime.
根据犯罪预警法第6409条规定
Under the authority of P.C. section six-four-zero-nine.
我们在大楼里面安置了蜘蛛监视设备
We are deploying spyders into your complex.
- 快点! - 妈妈 我好害怕
- Go, go, go, go. - Mummy, I'm scared.
我害怕 妈妈
Mummy, I'm scared.
- 妈妈 - 别怕 睁开眼睛
- Mummy. - Just scanning. Keep your eyes open, just open.
不要乱跑 睁开眼睛 没事的
Stay still, baby. Open your eyes. It's okay.
- 不用讨厌它 - 别乱跑
- I don't like it. - Stay still. Stay still.
我告诉你我在哪了 离我远点
I told you where I was. Get off my back!
你是个笨人
You are no good liar.
- 我知道你昨晚和谁在一起! - 你这个疯子...
- I know you were with that ho last night! - You wacky wi...
离我远点!
Leave me alone!
一人从热成像图消失
We lost one.
收到!
Roger that!
或者那仅仅是只猫跳过了窗户 或是什么其他的
Maybe it was a cat jumped trough a window, or something.
真是只可怕的大猫...
It's an awful big cat...
弗雷彻
Fletcher.
我去看看
I'll go check it out.
哪有什么犯罪份子 你们在制造恐惧 绝对在制造恐惧
If there's a crime in the rise up. Your terrify. They're absolutely terrified right now.
不想让你孩子受惊的话 离我远点
If you don't want you kids to know terror keep them away from me.
等等...大猫回来了
Wait a minute...the big cat's back.
你们觉得呢? 一个醉鬼 还醒不来?
What do you guys think, a drunk maybe, can't wake up?
是啊 或者是某个家伙不想被检查罢了
Yeah. Or some guy who doesn't want to get read.
居民们 保持安静关上门回到屋里去
Folks, please be quit. Close your doors get back inside.
找到一个验证身份 不是他
We got an ID. It's not him.
- 收队 - 去吃东西
- Standing down. - Let's eat!
弗雷彻 你看
Fletcher! Take a look.
- 房间里有4个人而不是3个 - 4个?
- There's four people in this room not three. - Four?
安德顿 克罗和一个戴墨镜的男人
There's Anderton, there's Crow and there's the man with the sunglasses.
窗户外有个戴墨镜的男人
There's the man with the sunglasses outside the window.
- 这里还有一个...在镜子里 - 对
- There's also someone here...in the mirror. - Yeah.
是个女的
Definitely female.
在联邦同意下 犯罪预防系统于2046年启动
The Precrime program began in the year 2046, with a Federal grant.
9年后的现在 哥伦比亚特区成为美国最安全的城市
And now, nine years later, the District of Columbia is the safest city in America.
什么原因呢? 因为犯罪预防系统很有效果
Why? Because Precrime works.
它取代了传统侦察系统...
Precrime has eliminated the need for conventional detectives,
所以系统的工作  是对潜在受害人的预知和保护
...so most of what happens now, is the verification and the protection of the future victim...
那我们可以见见预测师吗?
Can we see the Precogs?
嗯 预测师拥有如此强大的天赋...
Well the Precogs have such a powerful gift,
... 他们需被隔离在平和的环境下 不受外界的干扰
..that they have to be kept in peaceful seclusion so as not to be distracted from the outside world.
这次参观将让你们了解 一些他们的日常生活
But this display should give you some idea of what their daily life is like.
预测师们一年会收到800万封邮件
The Precogs get over eight million pieces of mail every year.
比圣诞老人收到的还多...
More mail than Santa Claus gets...
每个预测师都有自己单独的卧室 电视和会客厅
Each Precog has their own bedroom, television and wait room.
成为预测师是一件很奇妙的事情
It really is wonderful to be a Precog.
妈妈的新男友昨晚又来了...
Mom's new boyfriend came over again last night,
...而且他不是个聪明的人
...and he is not very intelligent person.
我妈会不让我到楼上吃东西
My mom wouldn't let me go upstairs eat in my room,
她会让我坐下来听那个人喋喋不休的一直说...
..so she let me sit down there the entire time having to listen to him go on and on and on...
该死!
Shit!
真该死!
Shit! Shit! Shit! Shit!
"身份确认 约翰·安德顿准许进入"
"Ident. John Anderton approved for entry."
不不不... 你不能来这里
No no no no... You can't be in here.
不不不...你要干什么?
No no no...what are you doing here?
不不不...别弄坏了那个计时器
No no no no...Easy there old timer who cleared you?
- 你不能进来 - 听着 华利
- You're not supposed to be in here. - Listen Wally.
我认识你吗? 你是谁?
Do I know you? Who are you?
我喜欢你 华利 所以我不会扁你 或者拿什么东西砸你
I like you, Wally, so I don't wanna have to kick you, or hit you with anything hard.
但是你必须答应帮我
But only if your promise to help me.
哦 嘿 约翰
Oh, hi, John!
你认得他吗?
What does that look like to you?
不认识
I don't know.
是阿加莎
It's Agatha.
他来这找她了
He's coming here to get her.
这就是她预知影像?
Are these all of her previsions?
我正在回传影像
I'm winding her right now.
跳过这些  帮我找里奥·克罗谋杀案的资料
I don't need to see all this, just take me to the Leo Crow murder.
我在查找 不会那么快的 我正在查她输出的信号
I'm looking. It's not coming up in any order. I'm getting what she's giving.
看到了吗?
Can you see?
- 他在里面 - 他戴了某种面具
- He's inside. - He's got some kind of mask on.
- 他从里面封住了门 - 该死!
- He sealed the doors from the inside. - Shit!
任何人不要在神殿里面开火 只准用黏液枪或者是警棍
Nobody fires a weapon inside the temple. Use only binds foam or your sick-sticks.
这里还有其他的出路吗?
Is there another way out of there?
我们已经包围了所有的门 他逃不了
We got all the doors covered, there is no way he's getting out.
约翰 出来
John! Move away from the tank!
约翰 别靠近乳业槽
Move away from the tank, John!
不不不...
No no no...
- 他带走预测师要做什么? - 你认为呢 先生?
What does he want with a Precog? - What do you think, sir?
没了预测师  他想杀谁就杀谁
He can kill whoever he wants to without anyone knowing about it.
但是还有两个预测师啊
But there's still the other two.
- 华利...华利 两个预测师还能起作用 是吧? - 你不明白...他们心智相通
- Wally...Wally! The other two can still function, right? - You don't understand... they're are hive minded.
三个在一起才有预知未来的能力
It takes all three for their predictive abilities to work.
意思是现在无法预知犯罪了?
Are you telling me they can't see murders anymore?
如果他带走的是这两个男预测师还好  但阿加莎才是关键
Maybe if he's taken one of the males. But Agatha, she's the key.
其他人都听她的 她最具有智慧
She's the one they listen to, the one with the most talent.
而且是她照顾其他两个
She takes care of the other two.
天啦...
Jesus...
拜托 找回她...
Please, bring her back. Plea...
找出那管道通向哪里 呼叫所有在地下的小队
Find out where that pipe leads I want every team underground now!
- 没用了 他赢了 - 不不 我会派些人到舱外 在蓄水池那抓住他
- It doesn's matter. He wins. - No no, I'll send some men at the EVA we'll stop him at the reservoir.
戈登 他杀克罗时她也在场
Gordon, she's in the room with him when he kills Crow.
她已经属于他未来的一部分
She's already a part of his future.
杰德 尽一切可能找出犯罪地点 我们要阻止这次谋杀
Jad, put everything you're got into finding that room and we stop a murder.
戈登 我们还有多少时间?
How much time have we got, Gordon?
还有...
We've got...
51分30秒
51 minutes 30 seconds.
你冷吗?
You cold?
明白我说什么吗?
Can you understand me?
你冷吗?
Are you cold?
你在颤抖是因为注射了药剂
The shivers are the drugs we gave you.
很快就会过去的
It will wear of soon.
很抱歉 我需要你的帮助
I'm sorry. I need your help.
你有一些我想要的信息
You contain information. I need to know how to get it.
- 能告诉我里奥·克罗是谁吗? 能告诉我吗... - 现在?
- Can you just tell me who Leo Crow is? Can you tell me if... - Is it now?
- 什么? - 是现在吗?
- What? - Is it now?
是的 最好马上告诉我
Yes... this is all happening right now.
我带你去一处公共场所 那样我得给你换点别的衣服
I gotta take you someplace in public, which means I gotta get you something else to wear.
我...已经厌倦了未来
I'm tired...I'm tired of the future.
"你好 雅克马托先生 欢迎再次光临"
"Hello, Mr. Yakamoto! Welcome back to the Gap."
"上次为您量身打造的衣服怎么样啊? "
"How's those assorted tank tops work out for you?"
雅克马托先生?
Mr. Yakamoto?
如果他想敲诈她 那该死的勒索信呢?
If he's ransoming her, where's the damn note?
跟勒索没关系
It has nothing to do with ransom.
他需要阿加莎掌握的信息
It has to do with the information that's inside of Agatha.
- 他试图证明他的清白 - 没有大量技术支持 他不能下载她的有用信息
- He's trying to prove his innocence. - He can't download her without a lot of technical support.
嗯 普通消费者是买不到这些技术的
Oh, well. Your average consumer can't buy any of this stuff.
随便买卖这些技术是要进监牢的
Because of it's been assembled and scrounged from spare parts made to warden.
但他购买零件 自己组合呢？
Assuming Anderton ordered this, who put it together?
鲁福斯·T·莱利是谁?
Who's Rufus T. Riley?
你喜欢什么? 我们这什么都有
What's you pleasure? We got it all here.
我们可以让你的运动梦想成真 还可以让你飞翔
We got sports fantasies. We got what I like to call "Look Ma, I can fly" fantasies...
包括从蹦极到如雄鹰翱翔于大峡谷的一切
...which encompass everything from bungee jumping to soaring like an eagle over the Grand Canyon.
我们可以让一个男人像女人那样享受性爱
We got guys come in, want to experience sex as a woman.
我们可以让女人和她钟爱的肥皂剧影星做爱 或者是...
We got women come in, want to get laid by their favourite soap stars. Or...
这里有无穷的乐趣
Here's some good clean fun.
这种感觉很刺激 但是又不会让您心脏病发作
It's a big rush, but you come out the other side without a heart attack.
我想杀了我的老板
I wanna kill my boss.
啊哈 可以
Uh-huh. Okay.
有什么梦想我可以帮你实现吗?
You got some images I can work with?
鲁福斯...
Rufus...
成为费城交响乐团的指挥
Uh, yeah, being concert master of the Philadelphia Symphony..
是我们最流行的选择之一...
Orchestra is one of our most popular choices...
不 我要杀了我的老板
No, I wanna kill my boss!
你这个变态 就是你这样的人 把我们的世界搞得一团糟
You sick bastard. You're the kind of person that makes this a terrible world to live in!
侦探 感谢大驾光临 现在好像全世界的条子都在找你
Detective. Nice of you to come down here. Seeing as every cop in the world is looking for you right now.
我需要你的帮助
I need your help.
为什么你老是抱着某种目的来这呢? 长官 我是可以打电话报警的
Why did you come all the way down here for. Chief, I make house calls you know that.
- 我和她需要帮助 - 哦 你好 宝贝
- I need help with her. - Well, hello there, honey-pie.
我很惊讶 安德顿 你在潜逃 但你仍然有时间和精力给自己...
I'm impressed, Anderton. You're on the lam, but you still got the time and energy to slice off a little...
...找乐子
...jerky for yourself.
- 她是个预言师 - 哦 是吗 预言师
- She's a Precog. - Oh...yeah...okay...she's a Precog.
你带来了个预言师?
You brought a Precog...here?
老天...
Jesus Christ...
- 你现在在感知我的意识吗? - 站起来!
- Are you reading my mind right now? - Get up!
将来的事我很抱歉  之前的事我是无辜的
I'm sorry for whatever I'm gonna do! And I swear, I didn't do any of the stuff I did!
她带有一些信息 我要你把那些信息弄出来
She's got information inside of her. I need you to get it out.
没门 哥们 我根本就不知道从哪开始
No way, man. No. I wouldn'd even know where to begin!
那些关于我堂妹艾琳拉的想法 那仅仅是想法而已
Those thoughts about my cousin Elena, they were just thoughts.
- 你已经两次因为犯黑客罪而被降级 - 所以呢?
- You're been busted twice for felony hacking. - So?
所以现在我需要你入侵她的意识
So now I need you to hack into her.
可以 但我要保留所有从她大脑里得到的信息
I tell you what. I do this, I get to keep whatever images I get from her head.
那些信息不属于任何人
They don't belong to anybody.
带她去沙克电台吧
Then take her to Radio Shack.
鲁福斯 你一定要帮我
Rufus, you gotta help me.
阿加莎 我要知道
Agatha I need to see.
我要知道我会遇上什么事
I need to see what's gonna happen to me.
这样我就可以采取措施了
And then we'll go.
- 哇 起作用了 - 慢点
- Wow. She works. - Slow it down.
我怎么慢点 砸她的头?
How do I slow this down? I should hit her on the head?
- 你录下来了吗? - 该死
- Are you recording this? - Shit!
好 开始录了
Yeah, recording.
这些我已经知道了 再快点 快点
I know this already. Come on. Move on.
再见 克罗
Good-bye, Crow.
怎么啦?
What happened?
- 不知道 - 怎么回事?
- I don't know. - What happened?
- 剩下的呢? - 我猜就这么点了吧
- Where's the rest of it? - I guess that's all of it.
我的少数派报告呢?
Where is my Minority Report?
到底有没有存在？
Do I even have one?!
有吗?
Do I have one?
没有
No.
- 什么? - 没有
- What? - No.
怎么了...怎么了?
What...what?
阿加莎 怎么了?
Agatha. What?
- 看到了吗? - 看到什么?
- Can you see? - See what?
安妮·莱夫丽...
Anne Lively...
你想让我知道谁杀了安妮·莱夫丽
You want me to see who killed Anne Lively.
- 录下来了吗? - 是的 但看上去像是倒放
- Are you recording this? - Yeah, but look it's backwards.
我热爱我的生活 一切都是美好的
I like my life. Everything is good.
- 他们来了 - 谁?
- They're inside. - Who?
全是你的老队友
All your old team mates.
- 查看房间 - 好的
- Chamber. Look in chamber. - Yeah.
不是!
Negative!
谢谢
Thank you!
- 你是天选之子 - 不不 你才是天选之子
- You are the man! - No, no, you're the man!
你看到那些伞了吗?
Can you see the umbrella?
拿一把 拿一把
Take it. Take it!
那个穿蓝外套的男人
The man in the blue suit.
他丢了他的公文包
He drops his briefcase.
你看到一个女人穿着褐色大衣
You see a woman in a brown dress.
她认识你
She knows you face.
这边
Turn in here.
走吧!
Let's go!
- 停! - 我们不能在这里逗留
- Wait! - No. We can't stop here!
看见那个卖气球的男人了吗?
Can you see the balloon man?
等等...
Wait...
等等..
等什么?
What are we waiting for?
等等...
Wait...wait...
Wait...
- 求求你了 妈妈 给我买一个 - 嗯 好吧
- Please, mummy, can we have one? - Well, alright.
等着
Wait.
谢谢
Thank you.
- 有人发现目标了吗? - 没有
- Anybody get an ID? Anybody? - Negative.
好吧 斯考特 雷蒙思 去查查那边 其他人跟我来 行动
Alright. Scott. Ramos. Take these dens there. Everyone else follow me. Let's go!
他知道 别回家
He knows. Don't go home.
我们已经盯上了
We've got eyes on.
- 等等 赏点小钱儿吧? - 给他点钱
- Hold. Please, please have you got a coin? - Drop some money.
你就不能放到我手里来?
Can't you put it in my hand?
上帝保佑你!
May God Bless You!
该死!
Damn!
就是他
That's the guy!
窗户上映出来的男人
The man in the window.
嘿 嘿!
Hey. Hey!
- 一间房加税是95美元一晚 - 介意我看看你的执照吗?
- Rooms are ninety-five a night plus tax. - You mind if I take a look at your register?
是啊 我介意...
Yeah, I mind...
那现在呢?
How about now?
您自己看吧
Help yourself.
他在这
He's here.
安德顿 快走
Anderton, leave.
你有得选择 快走 就是现在
You have a choice. Walk away. Right now.
不行 我得知道我的生活出了什么问题
I can't. I have to know. I have to find out what happened to my life.
拜托
Please.
阿加莎 我不会杀死那个男人的 我甚至不认识他
Agatha. I'm not going to kill the man. I don't even know him.
- 克罗在哪个房间? - 1006.
- What room is Crow in? - 1006.
快点
Come on.
错了
Wrong room.
离开这
Leave.
Leave!
噢 上帝...
Oh, God...
是肖恩 我的儿子
This is Sean. My son.
这6年里每一天我都想着两件事情
Every day for the last six years I've thought about only two things.
第一件是如果我的儿子活着的话 现在会长成什么样子
The first was what my son would look like if he were alive today.
如果我在大街上碰到他 我是否还认得出他
If I would even recognize him if I saw him on the street.
第二件事是我该如何处置那个带走我儿子的人
The second was what I would do to the man who took him.
你是对的
You were right.
我没有被陷害
I'm not being set up.
你必须带我回去
You have to take me home!
正如你所说 没有少数派报告 我也没有可以选择的未来
You said so yourself, there is no Minority Report. I don't have an alternate future.
我要杀了这个人
I am going to kill this man.
你仍然有选择
You still have a choice.
其他人看不到他们的未来 你还有选择
The others never saw their future. You still have a choice!
里奥·克罗?
Leo Crow?
你是谁?
Who the hell are you?
6年前 巴尔的摩市 你在西伦敦富兰克公众泳池抢走一个孩子
Six years ago. Baltimore. You grabbed a kid at Francis public pool in the West End.
我有吗? ...我不知道 你说什么公众场所...
Did I? I don't know... I don't know a thing about a public place...
我是谁? ! 我是谁? !
Who am I?! Who am I?!
你是某人的父亲
You're someone's father.
他的名字叫肖恩!
His name is Sean!
我跟他说我是个警察...
I told him I was a policeman...
我跟他说需要他的帮助 这个谎言不错吧
I told him I needed his help. Wasn't so bad.
我给他唱歌听 还给他饼干吃
I sang him a song and bought him a pretzel. I bought him a pretzel.
他很开心!
He was happy! He was happy!
他还活着吗?
Is he still alive?
还活着吗? !
Is he alive?!
你把他藏哪了? 他还好吗?
Where have you got him? Is he all right?
告诉我 你这个混蛋...他在哪? !
Tell me, you fuck...where is he?!
我把他装到一个桶里 然后沉入大海
I put him in a barrel. I sunk him in the bay.
但桶又浮上来 我就把他抱出来了... 我很温柔吧...
It floated back up. I took him out... I was gentle...I was gentle...
我对他很温柔
I was gentle.
我很抱歉 抱歉...
I'm sorry! I'm sorry...
十分的抱歉...
I'm so very sorry...
你为什么要这么做?
Why did you do that to me?
你可以选择
You can choose.
你可以选择...
You can choose...
你有权保持沉默
You have the right to remain silent.
但你所说的每一句话都将作为呈堂证供
Anything you say or do can be used against you in a court of law.
未来的任何审判你都有权请律师为你辩护
You have the right to an attorney now, and during any further questioning.
如果你不能负担律师的费用
If you can't afford an attorney,
我们将为你指派一位
...we will appoint one.
你明白这些权利吗?
Do you understand these rights?
你不杀我了吗?
You're not gonna kill me?
- 你清楚这些... - 你不杀我了吗?
- You understand these... - You're not gonna kill me?
...权利?
...rights?
如果你不杀我 我的家人将什么也得不到!
If you don't go through with this my family gets nothing!
知道吧?
Okay?
- 你该杀了我 他说你会的 - 他?
- You're supposed to kill me. He said you would. - He?
"他"是谁?
Who's he?
我不知道
I don't know.
他打电话到我的囚室
He called me in my cell.
他说我会被释放 如果我死了 我的家人将会得到很好的照顾
He told me I would be released, if I went along, and my family would be taken care of.
如果什么? 如果你怎样?
If you what? If you did what?
如果我表现得像杀了你儿子
If I acted like I killed your kid.
清楚了吗?
Okay?
如果你杀了我的儿子? !
If you killed my kid?!
你不杀我 我的家人就什么也得不到
Look, you don't kill me, my family gets nothing. Okay?
那这照片是怎么回事?
What about the pictures?
是假的 他给我的 明白了吧?
They're fake. He gave them to me. Okay?
你得告诉我"他"是谁? 谁安排的?
Listen to me. Listen to me. You tell me who was it, set this up?
我不知道
I don't know.
-杀了我 -我再问你一遍 谁派你来的?
- Come on! - I'm asking you again. Who was who put you up?
我没看到他的脸
I didn't see his face.
- 我要是告诉你了 我家人就什么都得不到 - 谁让干的?
- I tell you who it was and my family gets nothing. - Who made you do this?
- 杀了我! - 快说!
- Kill me! - Tell me!
里奥 松开枪 松开枪
Let go of the gun. Leo, let go of the gun.
松开枪 没事的
Let go of the gun. It's okay.
松开枪 那才对
Let go of the gun. That's it.
松开枪
Let go of the gun.
你不杀我...
You're not gonna kill me...
再见 克罗
Good-bye, Crow.
安德顿 等等!
Anderton! Wait a second!
这说不通
Doesn't make sense.
如果你是个儿童杀手 拍了这些照片
If you were a child killer, you took these pictures,
你会把它们扔在床上让人发现吗?
...would you leave them on the bed for anyone to find?
照片可能是收好的  但被安德顿摆在床上
They may have been put away, Anderton might have found them.
你之前是在哪个部门?
What kind of cop were you before this?
经济犯罪部 干了8年
Treasury Agent, eight years.
- 这是你第一次来到谋杀现场吧 - 是啊
- This would be your first actual murder scene. - Yeah.
在调去联邦之前我是专管杀人案的
I worked homicide before I went federal.
这就是我们所说的"刻意的证据"
This is what we would we call an "orgy of evidence".
- 你知道我接手过多少有刻意证据的谋杀案? - 多少?
- You know how many orgies I had as a homicide cop, Gordon? - How many?
一个都没有
None.
这是蓄意谋杀
This was all arranged.
今天我们目睹自犯罪预防试验开始后6年的第一宗谋杀案
"Today we saw the first murder in the six years of the Precrime experiment."
"这是人类悲惨的失败"
"Sadly enough this failure was human."
"保护小组没有及时阻止这宗谋杀"
"The protection team simply didn't get their in time, to stop the murder."
"但是这宗谋杀跟预言师预测的一样"
"But the murder itself happened exactly as the Precogs predicted it would."
"我认为今天的人类过于依赖犯罪预警系统了"
"I think that today is bank on the human face on the Precrime system."
- 达尼·维特找你 - "甚至系统也显示..."
- Danny Witwer's on the phone. - "It shows that even if the system..."
- 他说有重要的事情 - "...我们不能过于依赖它"
He says it's important. - "...we are not."
- "我提醒你预防犯罪..." - 拉马...
- "I remind you however, that the Precrime..." - Lamar...
"...成功的阻止了成百上千宗谋杀"
"...still successfully intervene in hundreds of indented homicides."
- 什么? - 拉马 有事大不对劲儿
- What? - Lamar there is something terrible wrong.
- 我们跟错了人 - 什么?
- We're chasing the wrong man. - What?
我不想在电话上说
I don't wanna say it over the phone.
在安德顿家见
Meet me at Andertons.
我们在里奥·克罗的房间里发现了这个
We recovered that from Leo Crow's hotel room.
我记得我是什么时候把这个给他的 是在巴尔的摩市
I remember when I gave this to him. Back in Baltimore.
坐吧 先生
Please, sir.
告诉我你的发现
Tell me what you have.
这是安妮·莱夫利凶杀案
This is the murder of a woman named Anne Lively.
约翰跟我说过这事
John told me about this.
- 是系统告诉你的? - 是的
- You got this from Containment? - Yes.
这个影像来自双胞胎阿瑟和丹谢尔
This is from the twins, Arthur and Dashiell.
阿加莎的影像不见了
Agatha's stream was missing.
这个是从安德顿的朋友那得到的
Now this one is from the cyberparlor.
安德顿从阿加莎的大脑中下载的
Anderton downloaded this directly from Agatha.
由鲁福斯·华利记录
And Rufus Riley recorded it.
- 是一样的预测 - 不全是
- It's the same prevision. - Not quite.
看看水面的波纹
Look at the surface wind across the water.
看那波纹..
Watch the ripples...
从岸边扩散开来
...moving away from shore.
现在看第二个影像
Now the second image.
这是系统提供的
This is the one from Containment.
也就是阿瑟和丹谢尔看到的
This is what Art and Dash saw.
看水面
Watch the water.
风向变了
The wind's changed.
波纹却改朝另一个方向扩散
The ripples are moving the other way.
这宗谋杀案是在两个不同的时间发生的
This murder is taking place at two different times.
根据门卫所说 安德顿在他被通缉前看过这些影像
According to the Sentry, Anderton was watching this at Containment right before he was tagged.
我怎么知道 他来拜访我 告诉我数据发生丢失
What I know. He came to me, told me about the missing data stream.
他担心你会发现
He was concerned that you might find it.
那他对了 我发现了
Well he was right. I did find it.
这些镜像一直在阿加莎的脑子里
It was inside of Agatha the whole time.
所以问题是 谁会想把这些从数据库里面删除呢?
So the question is, why would someone want this erased from the data file?
丹尼 听着 告诉我你在想什么
Danny, listen, tell me what you're thinking.
- 我在想有人逃脱了罪责 - 怎么逃?
- I'm thinking someone got away with murder. - How?
杰德跟我说过 有时候预言师们不止一次看到相同的谋杀?
Well Jad told me that sometimes the Precogs see the same murder more than once?
这个叫镜像反射
It's called an echo.
杰德管这个叫预言师幻觉记忆...
Jad called it Precog deja vu...
- 我们教技术员确定影像类型 避免错误... - 是啊 但是...
- Well we teach the tech's to identify them and disregard... - Yeah but...
技术员怎么知道那仅仅是镜像反射?
What if the technician only thought he was looking at an echo?
万一他们看到的是另一宗谋杀案 但又无法区分呢?
What if what he was really looking at was a completely different murder all together?
我不明白
I don't understand.
凶手所要做的就是雇人杀了安妮·莱夫利
All he would have to do is to hire someone to kill Anne Lively.
雇那些流浪汉 瘾君子 那些一无所有的人
Someone like a drifter, a neuroin addict, someone with nothing to lose.
犯罪预警阻止凶案的发生
Precrime stops the murder from taking place.
警察抓住凶手 带走他
Hails the killer, takes him away,
但是就在那时
...but then, right then,
另外一个人又重演了这个预言
...someone else has reviewed the Prevision.
穿着同样的衣服 以完全相同的方式犯案
And dress in the same clothes commits a murder in exactly the same way.
技术师看了看 以为是镜像反射 就把它删除了
Technician takes a look, think he's looking at an echo. Erases it.
当然这仅限于有权使用犯罪预警的一把手
Of course it would have to be someone with access to the Previsions in the first place.
- 一个处于高职位的人... - 嘘 你知道我听到什么了吗?
- Someone fairly high up... - Shhh. Do you know what I hear?
什么也没有
Nothing.
没有上楼的脚步声
No footsteps up the stairs.
没有气垫船驶过窗外的声音 甚至连蜘蛛追踪器的嘀哒声都没有
No hovercraft out the window and no clickity click of little spyders.
你知道我为什么听不到那些声音吗 丹尼?
Do you know why I can't hear any of those things, Danny?
因为现在 预言师预测不到这件事
Because right now, the Precogs can't see a thing.
看到了吧 这很美
Can you see? It's beautiful.
- 我们去哪? - 安全的地方
- Where are we going? - Some place safe.
- 伯吉斯 - 拉马 我是拉拉
- Burgess. - Lamar, it's Lara.
- 什么事 拉拉 - 你得帮他
- Yes, Lara. - You have to help him.
- 他来你那了? - 是
- Is he there? - Yes.
- 他和预言师在一起? - 是的
- Has he got the Precog with him? - Yes.
留住他们 我马上来
Keep them there. I'm on my way.
求求你 别跟丹尼说 我信不过他
Please, please, don't tell Danny Witwer. I don't trust him.
我不会说的
I won't say a word.
别让约翰走了 好吧?
You just don't let John leave. All right?
- 他不是杀手 拉马 - 我知道
- He's no killer, Lamar. - I know.
好冷
It's cold.
拉拉 这是阿加莎
Lara. This is Agatha.
还记得我...
Remember when I...
...我给你和肖恩读"汤姆·索尼亚历险记"吗?
...I would read Tom Sawyer to you and Sean?
但读到汤姆和贝基在山洞里迷路了时 肖恩怕的不得了
He got so scared, when Tom and Becky were lost in the cave.
就像我一坐下...
It's like I sit down...
就能感觉到他的害怕
Gotta figure this out.
他们在利用肖恩
They used Sean.
好让我以为是克罗杀了他..
They wanted me to think Crow killed him...
但是他没有杀他
But he didn't.
他没有
He didn't.
他们为什么要陷害你?
Why would they set you up?
因为我发现了关于她的...
Because I found out about her...
关于谁?
About who?
为什么我没想到这些?
How could I not have seen this?
想到什么?
See what?
安妮·莱夫利...
Anne Lively...
阿加莎
Agatha.
赫里曼博士曾经说:" 死人常在"
Dr. Hineman once said "The dead don't die."
"他们守护着我们"
"They look on and help."
记住这一点 约翰
Remember that, John.
- 阿加莎 - 肖恩...
- Agatha. - Sean...
他现在在沙滩上
He's on the beach now.
脚淌在水中
A toe in the water.
他要你和他在一起
He's asking you to come in with him.
他正和他的母亲在沙滩上打闹
He's been racing his mother up and down the sand.
这间房子里充满了如此多的爱
There's so much love in this house.
他10岁了
He's ten years old.
他被小动物包围着
He's surrounded by animals.
他想做个兽医
He wants to be a vet.
你给他养了一只兔子
You keep a rabbit for him.
一只鸟 和一只狐狸
A bird and a fox.
他上高中
He's in high school.
他喜欢跑步 爱他的父亲
He likes to run. Like his father.
他可以跑两英里而不用休息
He runs the two mile and the long relay.
他23岁了 上了大学
He's twenty-three, he's at a University.
他和一个叫克莱尔的漂亮女孩恋爱了
He makes love to a pretty girl named Claire.
他向她求婚
He asks her to be his wife.
他打电话来这里跟拉拉说谁在哭泣...
He calls here and tells Lara who cries...
他仍然跑步
He still runs.
穿过校园 跑在约翰可以看到他的运动场上
Across the University and in the stadium where John watches.
噢 天...他跑得如此之快 就像他的爸爸一样
Oh, God...he's running so fast just like his daddy.
他看见了他的爸爸 ...
He sees his daddy...
他想跑过去
...he wants to run to him...
但他只有6岁 他还办不到
..but he's only six years old and he can't do it.
而那个人却是如此之快
And the other man is so fast.
这间房子里充满了爱
There was so much love in this house.
我好想他回到家...
I want him back so bad...
她也是
So did she.
难道你感觉不到吗?
Can't you see?
她只是想让她的宝贝回来
She just wanted her little girl back.
但是太晚了
But it was too late.
那个小女孩已经不存在了
The little girl was already gone.
她还活着
She's still alive.
她没有死
She didn't die.
但她也没有活着
But she's not alive.
阿加莎
Agatha.
告诉我
Just tell me.
谁杀了你妈妈?
Who killed your mother?
谁杀了安妮·莱夫利?
Who killed Anne Lively?
对不起 约翰 但是你必须再次逃跑了
I'm sorry, John, but you gonna have to run again.
- 什么? - 快跑!
- What...? - RUN!
我爱你!
I love you!
来吧 没事的 没关系 你会没事的 安德顿太太
Come on. It's okay. It's okay. You'll be fine Mrs. Anderton.
- 不! - 别动
- No! - Stay with me. Stay with me.
约翰·安德顿
John Anderton.
遵照哥伦比亚特区犯罪预防部的命令
By mandate of the District of Columbia, Precrime division..
我以杀害里奥·克罗和 丹尼·维特沃的名义拘捕你
I'm placing you under arrest for the murders of Leo Crow and Danny Witwer...
这才对... 这才是我的乖女孩
That's it... that's my girl...
我好担心你
I were so worried about you.
他有没有伤害你?
Did he hurt you?
天呐 我真想你...
God, I missed you so much...
没事了 华利在这
It's okay. Wally is here.
华利在这...
Wally is here...
你现在由我处置了 约翰 欢迎光临
You're part of my flock now, John. Welcome.
里面其实很舒服
It's actually kind of a rush.
他们说你会看到你的一辈子在眼前浮现
They say you have visions, that your life flashes before your eyes.
你的梦想都会成真
That all your dreams come true.
这都是我的错
This is all my fault.
在这件事上 任何人都无能为力
There was nothing anyone could do.
我猜你可能需要这些
I thought you might want to have those.
我好多年没穿这个了 我想确定今晚穿是否还合身
I haven't worn this in years. I just wanted to make sure it fits before tonight.
你看上去很棒
You look great.
我知道他曾经有过麻烦 但是我却什么都帮不上
I knew he was having trouble for some time, and yet I did nothing about it.
打扰一下 今日美国的记者来了
Excuse me. The guy from USA Today is here.
告诉他现在不行
Tell him not now.
- 他只需要几分钟时间... - 现在不行!
- He just wanted a few minutes before... - Not now!
我以为你已经退休了
I thought you were retiring?
是啊 的确是
Well I was.
但是约翰的意外让我认识到整个制度的脆弱
But this incident with John made me realize the fragility of all this.
这是约翰留给我的启示
This is John's legacy as much as it is my own.
现在我有义务保全它
Now I have an obligation to protect that.
拉拉...
Lara...
我知道这对你来说很困难 但是...
I know how difficult this is for you. But...
也许你可以给这件事划上句号...
Maybe you can find some closure in the fact that...
但事实上约翰发现了杀你儿子的凶手
...John finally found the man who killed your son.
安妮·莱夫利是谁?
Who's Anne Lively?
谁?
Who?
安妮·莱夫利 在被抓之前约翰正提到她
Anne Lively. John was talking about her right before they took him.
我不知道她是谁?
I don't know who that is.
约翰说他被陷害是因为 他发现了一些关于她的线索
John said something about him being set up because he "found out about her."
我们都知道约翰为什么被捕
We know why John was tagged.
他还说克罗只是一个替死鬼
He also said Crow was a fake.
维特沃呢? 他是在约翰的办公室里被约翰的枪打死的
And Witwer? He was killed with John's gun inside John's apartment...
拉马
Lamar.
你知道约翰为什么来此为你工作?
Do you know the reason why John came here to work for you?
- 为了肖恩? - 是的 他来为你效力...
- Sean...? - Yes. He came here to work for you..
因为他觉得如果他那样做...
..because he thought if he could just...
就可以阻止这样的悲剧发生了
...stop that kind of thing from happening.
- 我理解 - 不 我不认为你理解
- I understand. - No. I don't think you do.
先生 他们希望记者招待会 在两分钟内开始
Sir, they wanna start the press conference in two minutes.
拉拉 约翰是我见过的最好的警察 某种程度上也是我见过最好的人
Lara, John was the best cop I ever knew, and in some ways also the best man.
但是他的灵魂被伤痛所扭曲 呃...
But the scars he carried around, well...
我知道他希望我们赞扬他的英雄事迹
I know that he's want us to honor the good things we remember about him.
我也知道为何他会娶你
I also know why he married you:
你和他一样顽固
You're as stubborn as he is.
拉马...
Lamar...
拉拉...你知道怎么系这个领结吗?
Lara...do you how ton tie one of these?
你能帮我一下吗? 你知道我总是很笨拙
Could you please give me a hand? I'm all thumbs you see.
听着 我会告诉你我的计划
Listen. I'll tell you what I'll do.
首先 星期一 我将调查维特沃的证据
First thing Monday, I'll look over the Witwer evidence.
而且 我会让基德查一下系统记录 看看是否有一个溺毙的女人叫...
And I'll have Gideon run the Containment files, see if anyone drowned a woman by the name of...
你说她叫什么来着?
What did you say her name was?
安妮·莱夫利...
Anne Lively...
但我从来没说过她是淹死的
But I never said she drowned.
- 先生 招待会开始了 - 我马上就来
- Sir, the press conference is starting. - I'll be right there.
我们稍后再谈
We'll talk about this later.
或许明天? 我会去乡村别墅
Perhaps tomorrow? I'll come by the cottage.
我想和我丈夫说几句话
I'd like a word with my husband.
你未被授权 是怎么进来的?
You are not authorized. How did you get in here?
女士们 先生们 这位是拉马·伯吉斯先生 新的国家犯罪预防部主任
Ladies and gentlemen, Lamar Burgess, Director of the new, national Precrime.
我代表全体职员 很荣幸的把这个献上 祝贺你 先生
On behalf of your staff, we would like you to present you with this. Congratulations, Sir.
哦 上帝...
My God...
你们怎么弄到这个的?
How did you get this?
我报销了您六个月的帐单
I padded your expense account for six months.
这把左轮手枪...
Revolvers like this one...
是在南北战争末期 士兵献给他们的将军的
...were given to Generals at the end of the Civil War by their troops.
弹夹里面有五颗镀金子弹...
The cylinders were loaded with five gold-plated bullets..
象征着国家分裂五年引起的破坏和死亡的结束
...to symbolize the end of the destruction and death that had ripped the country apart for five years.
女士们 先生们
Ladies and gentlemen.
随着犯罪预警的全国性普及...
With Precrime going national...
也许我们就能期盼一个...
...maybe we can all look forward to a time when none of us...
一个没有枪炮暴力时代的来临
...will have to discharge another firearm ever again.
好好享受吧 这是命令!
Enjoy yourself. Enjoy yourself! That's an order!
这是否意味着我们可以 在周末享受湖边小屋的浪漫了?
Does this mean we can finally use the lake house on weekends?
喂?
Hello?
是的 稍等
Yes. Right away.
打扰一下
Excuse me.
- 先生... - 有事吗?
- Sir... - Yes?
先生 有专线紧急电话
Sir, you have an emergency call on your private line.
- 喂 我是伯吉斯 - 喂 拉马
- Yes. This is Burgess. - Hello, Lamar.
我只是想祝贺你 你成功了
I just wanted to congratulate you. You did it.
你创造了一个没有谋杀的世界
You're created a world without murder.
先生 每个人都希望您在他们的帽子上签名 您能给我们签几个吗?
Sir. Everyone wants your name on a hat, can you sign these for us?
你能做的就是杀掉一些人来达到你的目的
And all you had to do is to kill someone to do it.
这里是A区 我是杰德
A-room. Jad.
杰德 我是拉拉 约翰需要帮助
Jad. It's Lara. John needs a favour...
我不明白你说什么
I don't know what you're talking about.
我在说阿加莎的妈妈 安妮·莱夫利
I'm talking about Agatha's mother, Anne Lively.
一个吸毒者 曾经有一个小孩但不得不丢弃她
Just a junkie who had a kid once and had to give her up.
但...奇怪的是 她戒毒了
But...surprise. She cleaned herself up.
她想找回她的女儿
And she wanted her daughter back.
她想要回阿加莎...
She wanted Agatha...
杰德? 你看到了吗?
Jad? You getting this?
这是一个单独的影像 只有阿加莎有 没有时间和事件的数据
It's a single stream, from the female only, with no time or incident data.
不管是什么 这不代表将来 而是已经发生的事
Whatever this is, it isn't the future. It already happened.
但是问题是 离开阿加莎 就不会有犯罪预言了
And the problem was without Agatha, there was no Precrime.
她总是三个中能力最强的一个
She's always been the strongest of the three.
你知道如果没有了阿加莎 一切都完了
You knew without Agatha,you had nothing.
没有了她 你就不会有现在的辉煌
Without her, you wouldn't be where you are now, standing there signing autographs...
杰德 你在干什么?
Jad, what are you doing?
杰德 你要拿它怎么样?
Jad, what are you doing with that?
杰德 发送之前最好先考虑清楚
Jad, let's think before you send that.
所以你得摆脱安妮·莱夫利 最好让她闭嘴
So now you had to get rid of Anne Lively, you had to shut her up.
因为她是你的绊脚石
Which presented a problem.
你要怎么杀掉她又不会被预测到呢?
How can you kill her without the Precogs seeing it?
很简单  利用你控制的系统对付她
Simple: use the system you control against her.
在知道预言师会预见这次谋杀的前提下 你雇佣了别人
So you hired someone to kill her for you, knowing full well the Precogs would see that murder.
你假装答应要让她们母子重逢...
You lured Anne Lively out to the lake...
借此把她骗到湖边
...with the promise of reuniting her with her daughter...
快跑...
Run!
快跑!
等四下无人之时... 你亲手杀了她
And then, when you were all alone... you killed her yourself.
使用和你的雇凶一样的手法
In the same way the Precogs predicted your John Doe would kill her.
你制造了这起看上去是一个镜像反射的谋杀
You made the real murder look like an echo...
你清楚技术师们会根据培训课程  忽略它
...knowing the tech would do what he was trained to do. Disregard it.
安妮·莱夫利就成了另一个失踪的人
Anne Lively became just another missing person.
拉马 你现在要怎么做?
So. What are you gonna do, Lamar?
你该怎么办?
What are you gonna do?
我们有一个红球事件
We got a Red Ball!
被害人
约翰 安德顿
想想那个女孩所救的人命
Think about the lives that little girl has saved.
想想她还会救多少人
Think about all the lives she will save.
那个小女孩本来能救肖恩一命的...
That little girl could have saved Sean...
你还敢说出这个名字!
DON'T YOU EVER SAY HIS NAME!
你利用我的丧子之痛陷害我!
You used the memory of my dead son to set me up.
你清楚我对复仇的渴望 从而堕入你的圈套
That was the one thing you knew that would drive me to murder.
你要干什么 拉马?
What are you going to do now, Lamar?
你现在要干什么 拉马?
- 你想怎么样...? - 让我闭嘴?
- How are you gonna... - Shut me up?
原谅我 约翰!
Forgive me, John!
行凶者
拉马·伯吉斯
拉马
Lamar.
都结束了
It's over.
你要问的问题是:
The question you have to ask is:
你打算怎么做?
What are you gonna do now?
- 预言师已经预测到这一切 - 是的
- No doubt the Precogs have already seen this. - No doubt.
你现在进退两难了 不是吗?
You see the dilemma,don't you?
如果你不杀我 那么预言师就错了 预警系统就完蛋
If you don't kill me, the Precogs were wrong and Precrime is over.
如果你杀了我 你就完了 但是证明系统是有效的
If you do kill me, you go away, but it proves the system works.
预言师是对的
The Precogs were right.
那你现在要怎么做?
So what are you gonna do now?
代价是什么? 仅仅是多了一宗凶杀案
What's it worth? Just one more murder...
你将会带着光环下地狱 而人们仍然相信犯罪预警系统
You'll rot in hell with a halo, but people will still believe in Precrime.
你现在要做的就是 像他们预见的那样杀了我
All you have to do now is kill me like they said you would.
除了...
Except...
你把握住你自己的未来
You know your own future.
这意味着只要你想 你就可以改变未来
Which means you can change it if you want to.
你仍然有选择 拉马
You still have a choice, Lamar.
就像我一样
Like I did.
是的 我还有选择...
Yes, I have a choice...
我已经决定了
...and I've made it.
原谅我 约翰
Forgive me, John.
原谅我...
Forgive me...
原谅我 我的孩子
Forgive me, my boy.
拉马!
Lamar!
在2054年 也就是犯罪预警计划实施的第六年 预警系统被取消了
In 2054 the six year Precrime experiment was abandoned.
所有的犯人都被无条件赦免和释放
All prisoners were unconditionally pardoned and released.
但是警察仍然在接下来的几年里 对大部分人实施了监控
Although police departments kept watch on many of them for years to come.
阿加莎和那对双胞胎
Agatha and the twins.
被送至一处秘密地点
Were transferred to an undisclosed location.
一个能从他们天赋中解脱的地方
A place where they could find relief from there gifts.
一个可以让他们...
A place where they could live out their lives.
平静生活的地方
In peace.